Prologue: After the Battle

Rio grabbed Charles Arbor by the scruff of his neck and dragged him down the hill in front of an audience of 5,000 soldiers.

Christina bit down hard on her lip, maintaining a composed expression as she watched on intently. Before long, Rio was right beside her, throwing Charles onto the floor without a word.

“Ha... Haha...” Charles had completely lost his will to fight. He laughed dryly.

“Is everyone else okay?” Rio asked, mainly looking at Celia and Orphia. Along with Vanessa, the two had been on the ground when he arrived.

“Yup. I was only hit a little, so I’m fine,” Celia answered. “Vanessa was only knocked out, so it isn’t anything life-threatening. Orphia... She had her magic essence sealed with an enchanted collar, but I removed it with Dispello.”

Celia currently had her hand over Orphia’s stomach as she cast her healing magic. Right beside Orphia was the collar Charles had placed on her—a magic artifact commonly known as a sealing shackle.

Like its name implied, it had the effect of sealing magic essence. In other words, it made it impossible to release essence from the body. However, it would be more accurate to say it was an item that absorbed the essence of the wearer, activating a sorcery that severely disturbed essence control and prevented them from acting freely. This was why it could activate automatically as long as it had a source of essence to absorb.

“I’m fine. Cecilia’s healing magic is taking effect,” Orphia replied with an innocent smile.

Just then, Christina, who had been watching the battle while checking on Vanessa’s condition, approached Celia.

“Stay still, Professor. Cura.”

She placed her hand against Celia’s cheek and activated her healing magic to ensure the area Charles struck didn’t swell up. Celia had said that she was fine, but, that was probably because she had been too focused on treating Orphia to notice the state of her cheek.

“Thank you very much, Princess Christina.” Celia was dazed, as though she hadn’t noticed the pain until now.

“Not at all,” Christina replied with a frown.

Meanwhile, Rio picked up the sealing shackles that were beside Orphia and approached Charles.

“Hahaha...”

He clasped them around Charles’ neck. Charles showed no resistance, letting him do as he pleased. He merely laughed brokenly, like he was trying to escape from reality.

Rio frisked Charles and found two more sealing shackles in his possession, confiscating them. There was also a rope suitable for arrest, so he used it to restrain Charles’ arms.

“Sara, Alma,” Rio called out.

“Yes?” the two replied.

“Could the two of you disarm the people lying around and gather them together? Then tie them up with a rope or something. There may be some who still have the strength to resist, so be careful.”

“Understood.”

“Leave it to us!”

Sara and Alma both nodded firmly before moving into action immediately. The enemies that Rio swept earlier were lying all over the place.

“Rei, Kouta,” Rio called out to the two boys standing around with nothing to do.

“Y-Yes?”

“Could you also help disarm the enemies and gather all their weapons in one place off to the side?”

“...Okay.”

Kouta and Rei looked a little nervous, but set off right away. After they left, Rio approached Alfred, who was unconscious.

I should cuff him twice, just in case...

If the wearer’s essence control was exceptional, it was possible for them to defy the effects of the sealing shackles and control their magic. It was difficult to use advanced magic in such a state, but Rio decided to use two sealing shackles in consideration of Alfred’s abilities. Afterwards, he tied his hands and feet together with rope, retrieved Alfred’s enchanted sword that had fallen to the ground, then left him there.

As for Rui...

Rio walked over to Rui and paused, a troubled look on his face. Should he restrain the hero, a disciple of the Six Wise Gods, as a prisoner? He was technically on friendly terms with him.

There was something else bothering him, too—the hesitation he felt from Rui during the earlier battle. When they exchanged those last few words before Rio knocked him unconscious, it almost seemed like Rui didn’t want to fight.

It seemed unlikely that Rui would resist and rage recklessly if he woke up to this decisive scenario. After a brief moment of thought, Rio carefully picked Rui up in his arms. In the end, he decided not to restrain him. If Rui still wanted to fight, he’d have to subdue him.

“Mmgh...” Rui regained consciousness, cracking his eyes open.

“Good morning,” Rio greeted a little awkwardly.

“Haruto... Ah, I see...” Rui said, immediately understanding the situation he was in.

“I don’t want to resort to violence, so will you be compliant?”

“Yes. I have no intention of resisting.” Rui nodded weakly at Rio’s question.

“...” Rio said nothing else as he headed back to Celia with Rui in his arms. Instead, Rui opened his mouth to say something first—and for some reason, quite happily: “It’s the first time in my life... That I faced someone head-on and lost, that is.”

“I’m sorry. I couldn’t control myself and had to knock you unconscious.”

“No, it’s strangely refreshing. Come to think of it, it’s my first time being carried in a bridal style like this, too. At least from what I can remember.” Rui looked up at the radiant sunset and chuckled in delight.

“I’m sorry...”

“Please don’t say that. It’s comfortable.” Rui’s laughter drew Rio into chuckling along with him.

“I’m glad you were my opponent, Haruto. Truly...” Rui mumbled softly, looking up at the sky.

Bonus Short Story

Professor’s Homemade Cooking

One day before the banquet in the Galarc Kingdom, at the dining table in the stone house...

“H... How is it?” Celia asked, watching Rio’s expression as he sat down across from her. In front of him was a plate of omurice covered in demi-glace sauce, the first bite of which he had just eaten.

“It’s very delicious.”

“R-Really?!”

“Yes. The chicken rice has properly accounted for the strength of the sauce, and the half-cooked egg is perfect. It tastes even better knowing that you were the one who cooked it, Professor.”

“Y-You really think so?”

“Yes,” Rio nodded with confidence.

“I-I see... Thank you. It was worth all the practice, then.” Celia giggled bashfully.

“You’ve been learning how to make omurice from Miharu and Orphia often these days, after all. I'm honored to have the role of taste tester. However, I do have one question...”

“Hm? What is it?

“You’ve let me taste test all your other dishes while you were practicing, so why was the omurice the only dish you wouldn’t let me taste until today?” Rio asked.

“W-Well, that’s because...”

“Because?”

“You said omurice was your favorite food, so...” Celia mumbled quietly.

“Hm?” Rio cocked his head, unable to make out what she’d said.

“O-Omurice is your favorite food, isn’t it? That’s why I only wanted you to eat it once I was sure it tasted good! Because I wanted you to say that it was delicious!” Celia blurted, her cheeks turning red.

Rio was surprised. “S-So that was why... Thank you very much,” he said with a smile.

“Y-Yeah.”

“It’s really delicious. I wouldn’t mind eating it every day. Will you make it again for me?”

“...Sure.” Celia looked down and nodded slowly.

“Hehe.”

A short distance away, several residents of the stone house were warmly watching over the scene at the dining table.

Chapter 1: Across the Border

Several minutes later, Rio woke Alfred and brought him over to where Rui and Charles were beside Christina. Celia was still treating Orphia’s wound just to be sure she was healed, but Sara and Alma stood guard near Alfred in case anything happened. Meanwhile, Vanessa had also regained consciousness and was keeping a watchful eye over Charles’ subordinates, along with Kouta and Rei.

Fortunately, no one that crossed swords with Rio had lost their lives. However, there were a considerable number of people who had been sent flying by his wind spirit arts and landed hard, resulting in severe injuries. Those people had been restrained, and the critically injured ones were allowed to be treated by the sorcerers.

“You’ve done it now...” Christina glared at Charles bitterly.

“What are you saying? Those should be my words. I knew you shouldn’t have been allowed to attend that banquet. You managed to go behind my back and join forces with such a monster,” Charles sneered weakly. His fighting spirit had been completely broken, but he seemed to have regained a little composure and could hold a proper conversation again. He shot a look of detest at Rio.

“Take back your words and apologize. Sir Amakawa is no monster,” Christina ordered with a frown.

“Ha! Hahaha!” Charles cackled wildly, then lowered his voice to an irritated mumble. “If only... If only that monster weren’t here...”

He hasn’t realized it was Celia who connected Princess Christina to me?

Rio brushed off Charles’ resentment with a blank expression and made a guess based on his words. Why Reiss hadn’t explained that to Charles, he had no idea...

Christina seemed to be thinking the same thing, showing a glimpse of a doubt for a moment.

“We’re still within the borders of the Beltrum Kingdom right now. While we’ve apprehended the target, it wouldn’t be a good idea to linger about while surrounded by the enemy’s army. The faster we cross the border, the better, but what would you like to do?” Rio asked Christina.

He looked between Charles, his subordinates nearby, and the troops waiting on the hill. It was up to Christina to decide how to deal with them, and what action to take next.

Christina thought for a moment, but quickly made a decision. “We’ll bring Charles and Alfred with us as prisoners. We’ll investigate the details later.”

“Oh? Then what will happen to me?” Rui asked, shrugging his shoulders in jest.

“We cannot take the hero around as a prisoner. If you wish to follow us of your own will, that would be another matter, but...” Christina trailed off, yielding the right to choose to Rui. Taking a hero captive could be seen as a political attack, so she had to take a stance that thoroughly showed her lack of hostility.

“I see...” Rui looked at Kouta’s back somewhat sadly as he expressed his intent. “I shall return to the capital, then.”

Kouta avoided Rui’s gaze by keeping his face forward, never turning back once as he stood watch of their surroundings.

“Are you sure...?” Christina confirmed, also looking at Kouta’s back.

“Yes. I have a lover awaiting my return,” Rui nodded, answering clearly.

“Ngh...” Kouta’s back shook slightly. Rio and the others couldn’t see his expression from their position, but Rei was sighing in exasperation beside Kouta.

“Kouta,” Rui called. He didn’t respond.

Rui continued speaking to his back. “I knew why you left the castle. I knew, yet I tried to bring you back while dodging the subject, but... It really is true that I acted out of concern for you and Saiki. That’s why I came after you. I wanted to see your face and confirm whether you’d be okay outside of the castle. Whether you’d be able to live well in this world from now on.”

“...”

“If you tell me you’ll be fine, I’ll believe you. I won’t try to force you to come back anymore. I’ll believe that we can meet again someday and wait. You’re an important friend to me, after all,” Rui kept speaking in spite of Kouta’s silence, when—

“I...!” Kouta raised his voice, keeping his trembling back facing them. His bitter words were not in the language of this world, but in Japanese.

“I’ve... I’ve always felt inferior to you. You transferred into our school from overseas, blessed with your looks and brains, and immediately became the school’s favorite. You joined the same club as Akane and I and before I knew it, you were closer to my childhood friend than I was... I was jealous of you. I couldn’t win against you in school, sports, or looks. Akane kept praising how amazing you are—each time, it filled me with so much jealousy, I almost hated you.”

“Kouta...”

“But you were such a good person, treating me like a close friend—I couldn’t hate you. Even when we wandered into this world unable to understand the language, you spent hours every day studying grammar and vocabulary to help us... Acting like we were the ones having a tough time when you had it the toughest out of all of us. That’s why...” Kouta bit down on his lip.

Everyone watched his back silently. While they could understand Rui’s words due to the automatic translation effect of his Divine Arms, most of them had no idea what Kouta was saying. Only Rui and Rei, who were Japanese, and Rio—who had Amakawa Haruto’s memories within him—could understand Kouta’s words.

However, it was clear even to those who couldn’t understand Kouta’s words that he was venting out his pent-up emotions.

“That’s why it was only natural for Akane to fall in love with you. Then you fell in love with her, too. But I didn’t want to accept that... I was going to go insane with envy if I stayed with you and Akane any longer. I hated myself for feeling like that—it was pathetic. That’s why I ran from you two. That’s all...” Kouta touched upon the truth and clenched his fists tightly.

“I’m sorry...” Rui apologized with a distressed look.

“Don’t be... It must have been hard for you, too. Akane’s slow on the uptake, after all. She never realized my feelings. But you did, and that left you stuck between a rock and a hard place. I’m the one who should be sorry. Sorry, for leaving without a word—it was only natural for you to be worried.” Kouta returned the apology, his face twisting as he held back his bitter emotions. It was at this point that he turned for the first time, facing Rui. “I’ll be fine. I’ll do my best to live well outside the castle. So there’s no need for your concern. Don’t worry about me. One day, when I no longer feel inferior to you, I’ll go see you guys... Thank you for thinking of me as a close friend all this time. You’re a precious friend to me, too, Rui.”

“Yeah. We’ll always be friends.” Rui looked down, nodding his head.

“Look after Akane. Tell her I’ll be fine.”

“...All right.”

“No, not at all.” Flora wiped her tears with her hands. Everyone else watched on with pleasant smiles, with the exception of one.

“Ah, I get that the two of you reuniting is a good thing, but I don’t quite get the situation here? Why is Haruto with Christina? And with so many other women...” Hiroaki said. With his position as the hero, he was the only one that could interrupt the reunion of the princesses without any hesitation. His eyes had widened in deep interest at the sight of Sara and the other girls’ faces, but he soon spotted the faces of Kouta and Rei—who were clearly from his homeland—and blinked at them in confusion. “Oh, are you two Japanese? You don’t seem like heroes.”

Kouta and Rei exchanged looks, then nodded awkwardly. “Well, yeah.”

“Hmm...” Hiroaki hummed without much interest. He then turned to the girls and greeted them brightly, directly addressing them. “Ah, I haven’t introduced myself yet. I’m Hiroaki Sakata. I’m what you would call a hero, I suppose.”

“...”

Sara and the girls looked a little confused, having not expected Hiroaki to introduce himself to them directly. Hiroaki’s succession of questions had completely killed the conversation. No one was sure how to proceed under such a situation, so an awkward silence hung in the air.

“Why don’t we head inside for now? I’ll prepare somewhere we can settle down and talk, so we can continue this there,” Liselotte suggested.

Thus, Rio and the others entered the fortress.

◇　◇　◇

Ten minutes later, in a meeting room inside the fortress, Rio and Liselotte’s respective parties met face to face. Everyone Rio traveled with on the way here sat on his side, while Duke Huguenot and Flora’s group sat on Liselotte’s side. Also in the room was Aria, Liselotte’s right-hand woman and attendant. Vanessa was also standing behind Christina instead of sitting in a chair.

Incidentally, Charles and Alfred were brought to the fortress prison on their way to the meeting room, to be confined there temporarily.

“Now, let us get right down to business. I believe the first thing we should share is our reasons for coming to this fortress. Does everyone agree?” Liselotte checked, looking around the room.

“Yes, I agree. Though I can pretty much anticipate Lady Liselotte’s reasons for being here,” Christina said.

As the daughter of the Cretia family and governess of the nearby city of Amande, it was fairly obvious that Liselotte had come to this fortress to investigate the movements of the Beltrum army near the border. What wasn’t so clear was why Flora, Hiroaki, Roanna, and Duke Huguenot were there as well. Christina had assumed they were in Rodania.

“As you may have presumed, the reason why I’m here is due to the large-scale movements of the Beltrum Kingdom’s army near the border. Princess Flora and the others just so happened to be with me when I received the notice... When I told them what was going on, they stated their desire to accompany me. I brought them here on my enchanted ship under the agreement that they would immediately return to Amande once we confirmed the situation,” Liselotte explained.

“Did Flora and the others have business in Amande?” Christina wondered, looking at Flora and Duke Huguenot.

Hiroaki took the initiative to answer Christina first. “Nope. We were confined in Galarc’s capital for ages after the end of the banquet, but then we thought we’d greet Liselotte on our way back to Rodania. Since we weren’t able to say farewell properly at the banquet.”

Because his goal in visiting Amande was to make a pass at Liselotte and hopefully bring up the topic of engagement, he looked a little guilty about his answer.

The Beltrum army appeared as soon as we got to Amande, so I haven’t been able to talk to Liselotte properly yet... Ugh, can’t those guys read the room? Tch, Hiroaki thought to himself.

“I see... I understand your situation now. Then I shall explain why we’re here next—is it all right if I do the talking, Sir Amakawa?” Christina asked Rio. The way she checked with him before anything else showed how much respect she had for him.

They didn’t have any kind of special relationship at the banquet, so those seated opposite them were extremely curious as to how they ended up this way.

“Yes, of course.”

“Then... I’d like to ask that you all keep what I say here confidential. Of course, I will report to Galarc’s King Francois myself at a later date, but the matters do concern the internal affairs of my kingdom,” Christina said, mainly looking at Liselotte.

“I understand. Shall I have my attendant step out, then?” Liselotte nodded, turning to face Aria behind her.

“Your Highness, if I may speak up...” Celia interrupted. The others could tell she was a young and beautiful woman, even with her hood covering her face. Since she was the only one who was wearing a hood in the room, the attention gathered on her was particularly curious.

“What is it?”

“It would be more convenient to have her present when you explain my circumstances later, so if I may be so bold as to suggest she remain present? I can explain the situation myself in a moment,” Celia said, looking at Aria.

“I see. In that case, she may remain present,” Christina agreed readily.

“I agree.”

Aria and Liselotte both looked a little curious at the sudden spotlight on Aria, but they agreed without any particular objection.

“Then, to get straight to the point: everything started when Vanessa and I fled from Beltrum’s capital, with the assistance of Count Claire. We tried to head for Rodania, where Flora was, by enchanted ship. These two boys were stowed away on that ship—they’re Rei Saiki and Kouta Murakumo, friends of the hero, Sir Rui Shigekura. We ended up taking them along with us, but I’ll omit the details of that for now,” Christina explained.

“Thanks to the Count’s assistance, we were able to make it to Cleia smoothly, but the problems began there. Duke Arbor discovered I had fled and immediately dispatched a search party led by Charles. We were able to quickly conceal ourselves in a secret room in the Count’s estate, but our movements from there were sealed. It was only a matter of time before we were discovered—which was when we met Sir Amakawa.”

“Ah... Wait, hold on. Isn’t that odd? You were blocked from leaving the Claire estate, right? And you were hiding in a secret room to avoid the search party, so how did he end up in that room?” Hiroaki interrupted.

“That’s because... May I leave the explanation of that to you?” Christina asked, looking at Celia.

“Yes,” Celia nodded, then removed her hood for the first time. She had secretly removed the artifact that changed her hair color in the corridor after Charles and Alfred were taken away.

“Professor... Celia?”

Sure enough, Flora opened her mouth in shock. Roanna, who was also a student of the same academy, had widened eyes too. Even Duke Huguenot was blinking in shock.

“Hey hey, who is that? Someone you know, Flora?” Hiroaki asked, his eyes sparkling.

“I’m Celia Claire. Daughter of Count Claire, and a former instructor to Princess Christina, Princess Flora, and Miss Roanna at the academy. Aria over there is an old friend of mine.” Celia introduced herself, then looked at Aria as she said her name.

“...” As an attendant, Aria didn’t say anything, but her wide eyes met Celia’s before her mouth tugged upwards in a faint smile.

That’s a shock, thought Liselotte. Aria had told her of Celia before, so she knew they were friends, but she never imagined they would meet in this way.

“Ah, and what do you mean by ‘professor’? You only look about as old as Flora and Roanna, or perhaps even younger,” Hiroaki said, staring at Celia closely.

“Thank you. But I’m twenty-one years old,” Celia said, giving her age a little shyly.

“W-What?! T-Twenty-one?! That’s older than me! Are you legal jailbait or something?!” Hiroaki yelled, standing up and leaning forward spontaneously.

“Gah...” Kouta and Rei looked a little disgusted at Hiroaki’s words. It was the moment they realized he was the polar opposite of the gentlemanly Rui, the hero they knew.

“Legal... jailbait?” Christina and Celia had puzzled expressions, unsure of the meaning.

We’re not going anywhere like this. Hiroaki’s continuous statements, which were made with no consideration of time and place, were giving Liselotte a headache. With no other choice, she raised her hand. “Umm...”

Everybody’s attention gathered on Liselotte.

“I happened to be present at the ceremony, but wasn’t Lady Celia abducted from her wedding with Charles Arbor? Why is she here... unless...?” Liselotte trailed off and looked at Rio with a gasp. He was the first she thought of with the ability to bypass the heavy security at the venue.

“Yes. I abducted her,” Rio nodded.

“I see. Indeed, if it was you...” Liselotte hummed in understanding.

“Sir Amakawa lent his strength in order to reduce the influence of Duke Arbor’s faction,” Christina stressed, speaking as though she had been the one who ordered Rio to abduct Celia.

This was the story they had discussed in advance for when they arrived at Rodania. Christina had made sure to warn Kouta and Rei against telling others before making this decision. That being said, it wasn’t entirely a lie.

Sir Amakawa lent his strength in order to reduce the influence of Duke Arbor’s faction, at Professor Celia’s request—the omitted information was that it had been for Celia, not Christina.

Christina had given her consent to legalize Rio’s actions so that the abduction wouldn’t be viewed as a problem, but that wouldn’t stop anyone who wanted to criticize Rio and Celia for not having Christina’s approval at the time of the act. In order to avoid this, they purposefully chose misleading words to make it seem like the act had been at the request of Christina herself.

The quick-witted Liselotte and Duke Huguenot instantly picked up on what happened and had looks of understanding on their faces.

“Huh...?”

However, only Flora’s reaction showed confusion.

“Is something the matter, Flora?” Christina checked.

“Ah, no, it’s just... Were you acquainted with Sir Haruto before, Christina?” Flora looked at Rio’s expression as she questioned her older sister.

Christina paused. “We weren’t directly acquainted, and there was a fair bit of danger involved in the process, so I’m afraid the events surrounding that are a secret. I can’t tell you,” she said, dodging the question.

“I understand...” Flora frowned with a frustrated look, staring at Christina.

Duke Huguenot took advantage of the lull in conversation to look at Celia and Rio. “If I may confirm, were you with Haruto this entire time, Celia?” he asked.

“Yes. She was present during the attack on Amande as well, under the name of Cecilia. Though I tried to avoid bringing her in front of everyone as much as possible,” Rio answered. This made Liselotte and Duke Huguenot’s eyes widen.

“Hmm... Ah! Right, she was there at that time! Wait, but her hair’s different! Even if she changed her hairstyle by tying it, how did she have blonde hair?” Hiroaki had been staring closely at Celia, but after a pause he pointed at her in excitement and started ranting. Her presence at Amande seemed to have been the hint that helped him finally remember her.

“I used a method to change my hair color.”

“Heh... Well, I’m surprised. It’s a pretty dramatic change,” Hiroaki said in awe. Right now, Celia didn’t have her hair tied up on one side like the last time she had been in Amande—her hair was down instead. Combined with the different hair color, her impression had changed quite a lot.

“We were pretty flustered when the monsters attacked Amande and I had no choice but to visit Liselotte’s estate...” Celia looked back on that time and smiled at the memory.

“I didn’t realize at all... But...” Flora muttered, looking at Rio as though understanding something.

“Neither did I,” Roanna nodded in amazement.

“You didn’t notice either, right Aria?” Liselotte asked Celia’s old friend.

“Embarrassing as it is to admit, no. I did feel a sense of déjà vu from her when we said our goodbyes, but... We didn’t see much of each other at the estate, and I never imagined she could change her hair color so naturally. If I had more opportunities to listen to her voice, I may have noticed,” Aria replied, analyzing the reasons why she didn’t realize it before.

“I see... Because there’s no way to naturally change your hair color. Or rather, no way that one would normally think of. It would be an extremely effective form of disguise in a society unaware of that possibility,” Liselotte turned to Celia and said with great awe.

“Indeed. That’s why we ask that you keep the existence of such methods a secret. Since it was an emergency, I had Her Highness and the others change their hair color while we were fleeing Cleia, but they don’t know the exact details of the method themselves,” Rio said, putting a stop to any prying before it could occur.

“I see... I’m curious, but it can’t be helped. I shall comply,” Liselotte agreed with a wry smile. Like she said, she was curious about it, but instantly determined that it wasn’t information worth being unreasonable towards Rio for.

“Umm... Sir Haruto, could you be using that method to change your hair color as well?” Flora asked Rio nervously.

“What are you saying, Flora? Were you not listening to the conversation just now? We just said that kind of prying was completely forbidden,” Christina said, shutting her down bluntly. Flora’s face paled, Christina’s words making her rethink her impulsive question.

“I apologize for her rudeness, Sir Amakawa,” Christina said with a sigh.

“It’s fine, don’t let it bother you,” Rio said with a soft smile and short shake of his head.

“We’ve derailed off-topic, but Sir Amakawa was able to sneak into Count Claire’s secret room because Celia was with him... as I’m sure you’ve all realized now. After that, we were able to escape the search party surrounding the estate and flee from the city with Sir Amakawa’s assistance,” Christina said, returning the conversation back on topic.

“Huh. So why did you come to this fortress? You were heading for Rodania, where you thought Flora was, right?” Hiroaki asked.

“We anticipated the shortest route from Cleia to Rodania would be heavily monitored by the search party. Plus, if we headed for Rodania through the Galarc Kingdom, we’d be able to shake off the search party as soon as we crossed the border. However, it seemed they were able to pinpoint our escape route through some means, and ambushed us with a huge army right near the border...” Christina paused, looking at Rio, Sara, and the other spirit folk girls. “Thanks to the help of Sir Amakawa and his comrades, we were able to drive away the enemy and capture their commander, Charles, and take Alfred as prisoner.”

“Ah, well, I won’t doubt Haruto’s strength at this point, but his comrades? You’re not talking about those two dull dudes over there, right?” Hiroaki glanced at Kouta and Rei before asking in the direction of Sara, Orphia, and Alma.

“It seems you’ve realized it already, but these three are my ‘comrades.’ From the right, there’s Sara, Orphia, and Alma. All three of them are skilled warriors that can use enchanted swords,” Rio answered in their place.

“Hmm...” Hiroaki hummed, looking at the girls with great interest. Sara, Orphia, and Alma looked a little uncomfortable at being stared at and avoided eye contact.

“...”

Meanwhile, Liselotte and Duke Huguenot had expressions of pure awe when they heard there were three enchanted sword users present.

“Wow, that’s seriously impressive. You all have such pretty faces, yet you can fight well too,” Hiroaki complimented with intense interest.

All the girls around me have lived such sheltered lives... Having a warrior position in the harem would be invaluable. Just by having them around, they can protect me, he thought to himself.

“Thanks...” Sara said on behalf of Orphia and Alma. However, she seemed to be thinking something on the inside, as she almost sounded a little curt. Perhaps he had sensed this, as Duke Huguenot immediately changed the topic.

“I see, so even Sir Alfred cannot handle four enchanted sword users. I almost doubted my eyes when I saw Charles and the King’s Sword captured as prisoners... How fortuitous,” he chuckled. Having an important figure of the enemy Arbor faction imprisoned was truly exhilarating—enough to make laughter surge up within him at the mere thought.

“That isn’t true,” Sara suddenly said.

“What do you mean...?” Duke Huguenot asked with a rare look of surprise.

Sara corrected Duke Huguenot as she hated being credited when she hadn’t contributed. “We merely drove back the other enchanted sword users that were present. The one who defeated that Alfred person was Haruto alone. In fact, the one who captured that man called Charles and drove back the army of 5,000 waiting at the border was Haruto alone.”

“Oh my...” Liselotte gasped in surprise, covering her mouth with her hand. The fact Sara and the girls had driven back other enchanted sword users was impressive enough, but the scale of Rio’s achievement was large enough to paralyze the senses.

Duke Huguenot had been speechless in shock, but he looked at Christina and asked for more clarification. “I don’t mean to doubt you, but what do you mean?”

“It’s the truth. Sir Amakawa defeated Alfred alone. Or rather, he took on Sir Rui Shigekura and Alfred together in a two-on-one battle—and won,” Christina stated.

“He took on the hero and the King’s Sword together... and won?” It seemed like that fact was far beyond anything resembling common sense within Duke Huguenot. He froze, at a loss for words.

“So he won against that nasty, handsome bastard, huh...?” Hiroaki’s brows twitched in reaction.

Nasty...?

Courteous and gentlemanly. That was the impression of Rui they had from watching him converse with Rio, so hearing Hiroaki’s opposite opinion made Sara and the others cock their heads in wonder. Meanwhile, Kouta and Rei were snickering at the bad reputation given to their friend and underclassman respectively.

“I hope this has clarified everything for you, Lady Liselotte. This is the reason why our army was deployed so close to the border. Though their aim was to capture me and they have now retreated, this doesn’t change the fact we have provoked your kingdom. We must have caused terrible trouble for you and your father. I offer my deepest apologies.” Christina looked at Liselotte and bowed her head deeply. It was extremely rare for a princess to bow her head at a noblewoman of another kingdom, but that extremely rare exception had come about because of her. She bowed her head as the princess of her kingdom.

“Not at all. Please lift your head,” Liselotte said to Christina in a fluster.

Christina paused for a moment, then slowly lifted her head. “Thank you.”

Liselotte exhaled in relief. “That aside, I wonder how they were able to detect Your Highness’s movements? If they were tracking you from the moment you left Cleia, then there would have been more chances to ambush you without waiting right until you reached the border,” she wondered aloud.

“The greatest reason is simply because they didn’t have the time, I believe. Every three days, Sir Amakawa and his group would use their enchanted swords to enhance their bodies and carry us while they ran, which substantially shortened our travel time. When the enemy caught wind of our location, we were around three days away from the border. After considering the group’s fighting capability and mobility, they probably wanted to avoid surrounding us in a forest or mountain area where we could quickly hide ourselves,” Christina said, giving her logical reasoning.

“Indeed, that hilly area is perfect for troops to hide at the foot of the hills while watching for anyone climbing them. If they had griffins in the sky, escape would be fairly difficult too...” Liselotte said thoughtfully, recalling the geography of the area. “But even with that taken into account, deploying an army so close to the border is an overly bold strategy.”

“Yes. That’s why we believe there was a counterplot behind that strategy,” Christina nodded, then frowned in frustration.

“Bold and cunning... He may be overbearing, but that Charles Arbor must be quite the commander,” Liselotte said in praise of Charles.

“I wonder about that... This is Sir Amakawa’s opinion, but I am in agreement—Charles may have been goaded into deploying the army so close to the border by a man named Reiss. The true cunning one behind Charles is that man.”

Christina brought up Reiss’ name for the first time.

“Reiss...? Isn’t that the name of...”

“The mysterious man who previously appeared before Princess Flora and Haruto when Amande was under attack, isn’t it? And also the name of the Proxia Empire ambassador...”

Liselotte and Duke Huguenot recalled the time Princess Flora was kidnapped during the commotion of the attack on Amande.

“Yes. We’ll need to investigate Charles some more, but that man is most likely the ambassador of the Proxia Empire,” Christina stated with certainty.

“Lucius Orgueil, was it? The man who abducted Princess Flora, the target of Haruto’s revenge, and the former noble of Beltrum Kingdom, now leader of the Heavenly Knights. I considered the possibility of Princess Flora’s abduction being an act of resentment, but if he’s connected to the Proxia Empire ambassador and Charles, then there’s a possibility Duke Arbor’s faction was involved in Princess Flora’s abduction,” Duke Huguenot suggested, bringing up Lucius’ name.

“It may be too premature to decide that... However, we will interrogate Charles regarding that as well. Although it could be possible that Duke Arbor was the one involved, and Charles may know nothing. We shouldn’t hope for anything,” Christina said with a heavy sigh.

Like Princess Christina said, we can’t expect much. If Charles knows nothing about Lucius, then the only clue left is Reiss. If this man is the Proxia Empire ambassador, then it’s more than possible Lucius is also connected to the Proxia Empire...

Rio turned his head over the whereabouts of his arch enemy. He couldn’t overlook the implication Reiss had made that Lucius was still alive—he had to finish him off next time.

“That aside, did you say the leader of the Heavenly Lions is Sir Amakawa’s target of revenge?” Great surprise lit Christina’s eyes as she looked at Rio.

“Well, yes. He’s the man who killed my mother when I was a child,” Rio confirmed, giving a short answer as though to hide the feelings in his throat.

“Oh... Is that so...” Christina fell silent and didn’t ask anything else. She had probably read the room, her expression like she was thinking of something.

“I’d like to question him about Lucius, so may I attend the interrogation as well?” Since his connection to Lucius had been brought up, Rio used this chance to make his request.

Christina closed her eyes and nodded slowly. “I understand. In that case, of course.”

“Thank you,” Rio bowed his head respectfully. Watching him from the side with slightly conflicted expressions were Sara, Orphia, and Alma. They must have been curious about Rio’s connection to Lucius. Flora had a similar look on her face as she watched Rio.

Christina seemed to notice Flora’s gaze, but acted like she was unaware as she looked around the room. “Are there any more questions?”

“Ah, yeah. Sara said something about Haruto driving back an army of 5,000, but I don’t quite get that. It’d be one thing if he was a hero with Divine Arms like me... But if he was up against Alfred and that bastard Rui, he couldn’t have taken on 5,000 people on top of that at the same time, right? I’m curious about how exactly the battle played out,” Hiroaki looked at Sara and asked about Rio’s fighting.

“The 5,000 soldiers were acting as a human wall before the border. They were only watching quietly as Sir Amakawa fought with Alfred and Sir Rui. When they saw the two get overwhelmed, they knew they wouldn’t be able to win against Sir Amakawa, even as a group of 5,000. He was that terrifying to see...” Christina began to speak about the earlier fight she witnessed, forcing down the various emotions swirling in her chest. She explained the situation at the time eloquently. “After Alfred and Sir Rui were defeated by Sir Amakawa, not a single one of those 5,000 soldiers stepped forward to protect Charles, who fled into their midst. They simply watched on as their commander was dragged away before them.”

“Hey hey, were those soldiers incompetent? Their enemy charged right into the middle of their formation, right? This isn’t some low-budget stage play, if you all charge at once you can kill him with your numbers. There must have been someone who thought that—heck, if I were the commander I would have ordered it. Oh, was it the commander who was incompetent?” Hiroaki complained, seemingly displeased by this fact.

“The soldiers present instinctively understood that they would be no match for Sir Amakawa. Even I feared him, and he was my ally—so I’m sure what the soldiers felt couldn’t be compared to me. Only those who were there would know what that shuddering fear felt like. It may sound like a dramatized heroic saga to those who weren’t there, but it’s the truth.”

Nobody wanted to die. No one would challenge someone in a battle they knew would end in pointless death. Those who did had either resigned themselves already, had gone mad, or were pure fools. Christina maintained an exceedingly serious face as she spoke to Hiroaki.

Ah, I’ve been thinking this for a while, but doesn’t this guy stand out too much? He’s always there wherever I go, snatching all the glory. He’s playing a bigger role than the hero, and now his reputation’s going to rise again? In front of Liselotte, too? Plus, he always has different women with him each time I see him... Don’t tell me they all belong to him, other than Christina and her lady knight? Tch... What a downer.

Hiroaki ripped out the dregs of his heart as he looked in turn from Rio to the girls all sitting opposite him. He didn’t like that the focus of the conversation wasn’t on him—the hero—but a regular knight.

“You must be a big deal if you could do that. Equal to a hero. No, since you defeated Rui, you must be better than a hero? Well, that’s if Rui was using his Divine Arms at full power, of course. But still, it’s impressive.” Hiroaki seemed to know that if he had completely denied these achievements, his own reputation would be affected. Instead, he begrudgingly accepted Rio’s feats.

“Yes, I think that was a tremendous achievement.” In contrast to Hiroaki, Liselotte offered her admiration with no ulterior intentions.

“I’m honored,” Rio replied, dipping his head at the two of them.

“This is essentially the story of how we arrived here, but there are some explanations I’ve omitted on purpose. I’d like to properly exchange information for the sake of our relationship with Galarc as well, so would you be willing to engage me in more conversation, Lady Liselotte?” Christina asked.

“Of course. I’ll need to make a report to King Francois and Father as well, so that would be most welcome,” Liselotte nodded pleasantly.

And so, Christina began to share the information she had.

◇　◇　◇

Roughly one hour later...

“Let’s end the discussions here. What should we do after this...?” Christina looked around at everyone in the room.

“The sun’s already set, so it’ll be difficult to head for Amande today. How about you all stay at the fortress tonight? It’ll take some time to prepare dinner, so if you would like to question the prisoners in that time, you may use an interrogation room. What would you like to do?” Liselotte asked.

“Alfred and Charles will both be expecting an interrogation. We may slip up if we rush into things recklessly, and it would be a problem if that allowed them to regain their composure. Let them stay in the dungeon today. If Charles’ pride is wounded, he may be more open to talking,” Christina said, taking into account Charles’ personality. She wanted to provoke him by delaying the interrogation in order to suggest he was a low priority on her radar. If he refused to speak after that, she would continue to leave him alone until his mental fatigue accumulated.

Liselotte understood Christina’s intentions. “I understand. I shall arrange for the two of them to be given minimal food and no information whatsoever.”

“Thank you.”

“You’re welcome. Now that we’re done here, please take some time to relax here until dinner. I shall have rooms prepared for you—though they may not be the most elegant. Do you have any requests regarding your accommodations?” Liselotte asked.

Flora looked at Christina. “Umm, may I stay in your room tonight?” she asked somewhat shyly.

“Sure, I don’t mind,” Christina nodded with a soft smile.

“Then I shall prepare one room for the two of you. I’ll also have Vanessa’s room assigned next door, to make it easier to stand guard,” Liselotte said, looking at the royal siblings warmly.

Vanessa bowed her head. “Thank you.”

“In that case, could we stay in the same room as well? There are some things we need to discuss with each other,” Sara raised her hand and said, looking at Alma and Orphia seated beside her.

“Understood. Then... How about a four-person room with Lady Sara, Lady Orphia, Lady Alma, and Lady Celia?” Liselotte asked the four to-be roommates.

“Would that be okay, Celia?” Sara checked.

“Yes, I don’t mind,” said Celia.

“If no one else has any requests, you’ll be given a single room. Is that okay?” Liselotte confirmed with the others.

“Yes, that’s fine with me.”

“Same here.”

Duke Huguenot and Rio both replied first.

“We’re okay with that as well.”

“Yeah.”

Rei and Kouta exchanged looks before replying.

Roanna hesitated for a brief moment before answering, perhaps out of concern for the hero Hiroaki and the royal siblings Christina and Flora. “I’d be satisfied if my room was close to Sir Hiroaki and Her Highnesses...”

Nowadays, she served as a caretaker for Flora and Hiroaki, but with Christina in the picture, she needed to show even more delicate consideration.

Hiroaki met Roanna’s eyes and shrugged. “I don’t mind.”

“Then I shall show you the way immediately,” Liselotte said, standing up and walking towards the door. The others followed her lead and stood up. Aria had gone ahead to open the door, when—

“Excuse me, Lady Liselotte,” Celia said.

“Yes, what is it?”

“With your permission, may I have some time to talk to Aria?”

“Of course. I was going to send Aria over after Sara and the others had some time to talk, but would you like to chat with her now?” Liselotte replied cheerfully.

“We can always talk at night, so please go ahead, Celia,” Sara said, Orphia and Alma nodding in agreement.

“Thank you... Then I shall take you up on your offer, if you don’t mind?” Celia asked Liselotte.

“Got it. Then you may stay in this room and use it. Aria, you’re off duty for the rest of today. Take your time and relax with Lady Celia.”

“Thank you very much,” Aria said with a faint smile.

“Cosette, Natalie,” Liselotte called to the two attendants waiting outside.

“Did you need something, Lady Liselotte?” Natalie responded respectfully.

Meanwhile, Cosette was casually trying to meet Rio’s eyes, smiling cutely once he looked at her as though to say “long time no see, Sir Haruto.” Rio flashed a brief smile and gave a short nod in response.

“Show the people of the Restoration and the two boys to their rooms. Princess Christina and Princess Flora are in the same room. Keep everyone else in rooms next to each other.”

“Understood.” Natalie and Cosette both bowed their heads.

“Chloe, you escort Sir Haruto’s friends to their room. They’ll be using a room for four, along with Lady Celia,” Liselotte said to Chloe, who was waiting nearby.

“Yes, My Lady,” Chloe nodded.

Once she confirmed that, Liselotte turned to Rio behind her. “Sir Haruto, I’m sorry to keep you occupied like this, but...”

“What is it?” Rio asked with a tilt of his head.

“Before I show you to your room, may I have a bit more of your time? There’s something which I’d like to discuss with you separately,” Liselotte said.

“Sure. I was just thinking the same thing, so it’d be my pleasure,” Rio answered immediately, accepting the private conversation with ease. Hiroaki watched them from the side with an unamused expression.

Huh? These two are ignoring me to run off and be alone...?

And he had gone out of his way to drop by and visit Liselotte, too. Was she prioritizing a freshly-promoted knight over a hero?

That being said, there were other girls that had his interest right now—Sara’s group. He was slightly discontented by the fact Haruto had brought them along, but all three of them were blessed with looks on par with Liselotte.

They were so attractive, it’d be a lie to say he wasn’t interested in getting to know them. Even during their discussions, he kept glancing their way out of curiosity. Or rather, he had no particular interest in the discussions, so partway through the talks he just kept staring at them.

Because of them, Hiroaki decided he would turn a blind eye to Liselotte and Haruto’s private meeting and instead use this chance to invite the three of them to tea while Haruto was occupied.

“Mmm. Ah, what should I do now? There’s nothing to do once I return to my room... Being a hero sure is boring,” Hiroaki suddenly started to say. It was unclear who he was talking to—or whether he was just monologuing—but his tone was incredibly exaggerated.

The parts he had emphasized were the fact he was free, and the fact he was a hero. It was an attention-seeking scheme to lure anyone with a slight interest in heroes—most effective when used against noble daughters. They would swarm Hiroaki even uninvited, which was why Hiroaki specialized in being on the accepting side and had no experience on the inviting side.

“...?” Presently, neither Sara, Orphia, nor Alma had any particular interest in heroes. They found the way Hiroaki suddenly cleared his throat and started speaking odd and cocked their heads slightly, but then dismissed his words as irrelevant to them and addressed their guide, Chloe, instead. “Could you show us to our rooms then, please?”

“Ah, yes. Please, come this way.” Chloe also seemed to find Hiroaki’s sudden actions strange, as she snapped back to her senses at Sara’s voice and resumed her duties.

“Pfft...”

That must have seemed hilarious to Cosette, who nearly burst into laughter. However, as expected for an attendant of Liselotte, she naturally turned her face away so that Hiroaki and the others wouldn’t see.

“Are you stupid?” Natalie whispered into Cosette’s ear.

“We’ll be resting first then, Haruto,” Sara said to Rio in a friendly manner as they left.

“Okay.”

“Come to our room when you’re done,” said Orphia.

“Understood.”

“We’ll be waiting,” said Alma.

“I hope you rest well,” Rio replied to the three of them as he watched them leave. He then turned around to address Celia before setting off himself. “Please enjoy your reunion with Miss Aria, Celia.”

...Celia?

Because Rio had addressed Celia without a title, those that hadn’t traveled together with them on the way here all looked shocked. That made sense, as there hadn’t been a chance for them to call each other by their names during the discussion just now. Flora was particularly shocked, blinking and frozen stiff.

“Yup. See you later,” Celia replied with a soft smile, after which Rio cheerfully nodded.

“We shall excuse ourselves first, then. If you need anything, please ask one of my attendants. Sir Haruto, come this way,” Liselotte nodded at Christina and Duke Huguenot’s group before calling Rio away.

“Excuse me,” Rio said, leaving together with Liselotte.

Ah, so that’s what this is. Well, I had a vague suspicion this was the case. So he’s in the picture already. I don’t know if they’re actually dating, but the slightest hint of another man is enough to turn me off. It’s unwanted real estate. Ah, that was unnecessary information, seriously, I did not need to know that. What a let-down. Ah, ah, ah...

It was indeed a cold wake-up call. Hiroaki was terribly dejected in his mind, lightly grinding his teeth as his mouth twisted.

What if Liselotte starts showing favor towards him too? What do they even have to talk about alone? Walking side-by-side like they’re showing off...

With an impressive amount of resentment over a misunderstanding, he glared at Rio’s back. He had avoided interacting with him until now, since it was difficult for him to gain the upper hand. He might need to consider a way to put Rio’s reputation in question, he thought...

Just as he was thinking that, someone who had been observing Hiroaki without him realizing it opened her mouth. It was Christina.

“Shall we go too?” she asked with feigned ignorance.

“Indeed... Roanna,” Duke Huguenot immediately responded. At times like this, Roanna was best at cheering Hiroaki up. Sensing Hiroaki’s bad mood, he had implicitly requested she take care of him.

Roanna quietly drew closer to Hiroaki and touched him, speaking to him from a close proximity. “Yes. Let’s go, Sir Hiroaki.” When he felt her warmth through his clothes, Hiroaki’s attention turned to Roanna.

Roanna really is great at things like this. And yet, Liselotte... What a shame. She’s acting like such a tease.

He had gone out of his way to visit her, yet she wouldn’t prioritize him. Displeased with this, Hiroaki sighed tiredly as though he was expelling all his rage.

“Ah, yeah. There’s nothing to do, but I’m a little tired. Let’s relax together in my room. Flora and... Christina? What will you two do?”

He seemed to be in a better mood now, as he grinned while winding his arm around Roanna’s shoulder before turning to Flora and Christina to invite them along. The brief pause before calling Christina’s name was probably because he was unsure of the state of their relationship.

“What will you do, Christina?” Flora asked, watching for Christina’s reaction.

“I have a small matter I’d like to discuss with Duke Huguenot, so you go on ahead. I’ll drop by once I’m done. Is that okay with you?” Christina said, smiling at Hiroaki gracefully.

“Well, I’m sure you have more information you want to share now that you’ve met up. I don’t mind. But I want to speak to you as well, so make it sooner rather than later.” Hiroaki nodded smugly, making a show of how generous he was. Now that she had joined up with the Restoration, Christina was on his side and not a top priority for him to win over.

Considering that, his attention was more focused on Liselotte and Sara’s group, whom he didn’t know when he would have another chance to interact with, but Christina’s smile just now struck him right in the heart.

“Of course,” Christina nodded cordially.

Nice. She’s got a personality that differs quite a bit from her little sister. A bit like a rose with thorns, but that isn’t bad, either. Hope we can chat soon.

Hiroaki was restless with anticipation. Thanks to that, he was able to drive Haruto out of his mind for now.

“Then I’ll have Roanna and Flora soothe my boredom with some conversation first,” Hiroaki said, pulling himself together.

“If you would like to have a discussion, you may use that open drawing room over there,” Natalie suggested to Christina and Duke Huguenot. It seemed the meeting room they had been using until now was right beside another one, on top of another door that had connected to a simple kitchen.

“Thank you for the consideration. We shall gratefully accept,” Christina said warmly. Her elegance was enough to enchant even those of the same gender.

“Then I shall prepare tea and snacks for you. Cosette, please show everyone else the way.” Natalie entrusted Hiroaki and the others to Cosette before heading into the meeting room first.

“Sure, no problem,” Cosette hummed, seeing Natalie off.

“I’ll see you later then, Christina,” Flora said reluctantly.

“Your Highness, words cannot describe how honored I am to be in your presence once again. I look forward to our next opportunity to speak together.” Roanna bowed her head low, expressing her respect for Christina.

“You’ve done well supporting Flora. Please tell me about everything that happened in my absence later.”

“Of course,” Roanna replied, happy to receive Christina’s appreciation. Then, she turned to Celia. “Professor Celia, I’m so glad to see you again too. I hope we can speak a lot later on as well.”

“Yes, it’s been a while, Roanna. I’m glad to see you again too. Princess Flora, long time no see,” Celia replied, beaming.

“Indeed, Professor Celia. And, umm, well...” Flora replied to Celia with a fleeting smile, stumbling as though she was searching for the right words. Rather than gauging Celia’s reaction, it was more like she wanted to ask something.

“Hmm...?” Celia seemed to realize that and cocked her head curiously.

“Let’s go, then.” Hiroaki prompted them to move, cutting off the conversation.

Flora ended the conversation sadly. “Okay... Please tell me your story later, Professor Celia.”

“Lead the way... Cosette, was it?” Hiroaki addressed Cosette as though he had to recall her name. However, Liselotte’s attendants had all caught his attention as top tier women, so he had memorized every one of their names and faces. He pretended he had to recall it because of an indescribable sense of shame that he felt.

“It’s an honor for an attendant like me to be remembered. Please, come this way.” Cosette smiled pleasantly, but immediately started leading them without any idle chatter. Hiroaki watched her back while humming to himself.

Hmm, Liselotte’s attendants sure have a high sense of professionalism.

Even when he complimented them, they seemed happy but evaded him with grace, and never fell for his attempts to catch their attention. He suspected it was because they were on duty, but thanks to that he’d had no chance to gather any personal information.

Since they rejected him in the name of their work, they were a bad match for Hiroaki’s style of waiting for an invitation. Which meant Hiroaki had to actively attempt to interact with them, but he hated having others realize he was one-sidedly trying to get in good graces with someone still indifferent to him. He had to be in the superior position at all times, which was why he passively waited for offers.

If only I could catch Liselotte, then her army of attendants would come along as a bonus, Hiroaki thought as he walked after Cosette, continuing to watch her back. When he thought of it that way, Liselotte’s existence was truly appealing. Remembering that she was with Haruto right now made his resentment return, though...

Wait a minute... Could Liselotte’s curt attitude also be caused by a professional mindset like her attendants? Maybe she doesn’t want to involve her personal feelings when interacting with me during her work...

Such a thought suddenly came to Hiroaki’s mind. It wasn’t impossible, considering how focused her attendants were while they were on duty.

Ah...

Hiroaki’s footsteps came to a stop.

Roanna immediately stopped too, peering at Hiroaki’s face beside her. “Sir Hiroaki?”

“No, it’s nothing.” Hiroaki shook his head and started walking again. Behind him followed Roanna and Flora, then Kouta and Rei.

Christina had been watching Flora’s back as she left, but then she addressed Celia as she started entering the other meeting room. “Then, we shall go inside the room as well. Until later, Professor Celia.”

This left Celia and Aria as the only ones remaining.

“After you,” Aria invited Celia inside the meeting room in an attendant-like manner.

“Geez, what’s with that? It’s just the two of us now, so you don’t have to be the attendant,” Celia said a little uneasily.

“Hehe. Now, let us go inside. I’ll prepare some tea.” Aria showed a rare glimpse of a soft smile and entered the room with Celia.

◇　◇　◇

Meanwhile, Rio had arrived at the room Liselotte led him to.

“I hope you don’t mind if we use the room I’m staying in. Please, go inside,” Liselotte said, opening the door and inviting Rio inside first.

Is it okay for a man to enter the room of a noblewoman? She doesn’t have her attendants around, either...

There had been situations where they met one-on-one in meeting rooms before, but Rio still wasn’t quite familiar with the etiquette of nobles. However, since Liselotte was okay with it, he was probably just overthinking things. More than anything, the fact they were alone like this was proof of Liselotte’s trust in him.

It would be weird for him to hesitate for too long, so Rio answered Liselotte’s trust by bowing slightly before entering the room. “Excuse me.”

The room was like a studio apartment with a simple kitchen, bed, wardrobe, table, and chairs to sit on.

“I’ll prepare some tea for you now. I’m afraid there isn’t much space, but please have a seat.” Liselotte pulled out the seat at the head of the table and offered it to Rio.

“Thank you very much,” Rio said as he sat down.

“No problem at all,” Liselotte said cheerfully, standing in the kitchen behind Rio. She began preparing tea with skillful movements.

It feels kind of strange... Rio thought as he watched Liselotte’s back. She had a strong image of being a noble lady, so seeing her pour tea was rather domestic.

“Do you often prepare tea by yourself?” Rio asked her as she heated water with a magical artifact.

“Yes, whenever I’m alone. I’ve rarely ever prepared it for anyone else though, so I can only hope this is good enough,” Liselotte said shyly, her cheeks a faint shade of red.

“It’s tea poured by you. I’m really looking forward to it,” Rio chuckled.

“Gosh, don’t put more pressure on me.”

Thus, they chatted idly until she was done and Liselotte returned with a tray in hand. The tea still needed to steep for a while, so they didn’t pour it out right away.

“Now, let’s get down to business—but first, I’d like to thank you for coming here.” Liselotte bowed her head at Rio as a preface.

“Not at all.” Rio returned the bow. “Like I said earlier, I had things I wished to discuss with you too... Though it’s more of a request from Satsuki.”

“Oh my, from Satsuki?” Liselotte blinked.

“Yes. The topic of Japanese food came up at the banquet, if you remember. Naturally, the food would taste better if we all ate together, so I wanted to invite you along, since you were present at the time.”

“It would be my pleasure.”

If Liselotte had been in the capital before meeting Rio here, she may have met Satsuki and heard already, but apparently that wasn’t the case. Liselotte grinned happily.

“The problem is when, where, and who else to invite along...”

Rio, Liselotte, Satsuki. The three of them were usually in separate locations, which made it rather difficult to make plans. There weren’t any convenient methods of communicating like in modern Japan where they could just call or text.

There were magic artifacts capable of long distance transmission, but the information would openly leak to anyone else with the same artifact within transmission range, so it couldn’t be used for private matters.

Codes existed, but communication was limited to those who knew the code, and there was a risk of the messages being deciphered. Highly confidential information was always to be passed through word of mouth—this was general knowledge.

If important people were to hold a dinner featuring unusual cuisine, it wouldn’t be strange for masses of nobles to hear about it and request their participation.

“Which means the planning will need to be done privately,” Liselotte immediately presumed.

“Yes. I don’t want the gathering to be too big, as it would be hard to enjoy the nostalgic tastes while worried about eyes surrounding you.”

“I completely agree,” Liselotte nodded firmly. This was her chance to enjoy food she hadn’t tasted since her previous life—she wanted to enjoy her fill without worrying about her surroundings.

“Which means, at the very least, Satsuki and Miharu would be included. Are there any others you would like to invite?” Rio asked, starting with the attendees.

“Let’s see... There’s no one in particular I’d like to recommend from my acquaintances... But I’d like to talk to your friends more. Especially Lady Celia and Lady Aishia. They helped out during the attack on Amande, yet I’ve barely spoken to them at all.”

“Celia and Aishia... Would that include Sara and the others too?”

“Yes. I’m sure Satsuki would want to meet them too, if they’re friends of Miharu as well... Also, if possible, I’d like to meet the girl who was always riding the bus in our past lives,” Liselotte requested.

Satsuki has actually met everyone already, during that time she snuck out of the castle while we were there for the banquet. Which only leaves Latifa, but...

Rio owed Liselotte a lot, and they were at least friends now. He would feel bad if Liselotte was the only one unaware of that fact during their dinner. And above all, he would feel guilty making the others act like they were meeting each other for the first time before Liselotte. It would probably be best to explain things.

However, the problem that came to Rio’s mind was Latifa.

He wasn’t certain, but there was a strong possibility the one who sent Latifa to assassinate Rio years ago was Duke Huguenot. Stepping into that territory might bring up traumatic memories for Latifa, so he had purposefully avoided that topic since coming to the Strahl region and becoming acquainted with Duke Huguenot.

Until now, she had mostly stayed inside the stone house and hadn’t been brought to any events involving nobility, but—

This may be a good opportunity for her to grow. To erase her past scars.

He recalled what Elder Ursula had said at the meeting before coming to Strahl with Latifa.

Was it really okay to make her mostly housebound, even though they had come to Strahl? Shouldn’t he let Latifa experience more things, for the sake of her future?

He didn’t know what was correct. But if Latifa wanted to meet Liselotte, he wanted to respect that as her older brother.

Rio thought about everything carefully before giving a rather optimistic answer. “It may not be possible to arrange, but I understand. I’ll ask everyone about it.”

“Really? Thank you so much!” Liselotte beamed happily.

“Not at all. Actually... that elementary school girl is my little sister,” Rio revealed.

“R-Really?” Liselotte was shocked.

“Yes. We’re not related by blood, but she was reborn into a rather complicated environment. Certain events led to me becoming her guardian. She’s a bright girl now, but she may harbor negative feelings towards nobility, especially certain nobles of the Beltrum Kingdom... That’s why she lives with some close acquaintances most of the time and doesn’t go out much,” Rio explained to Liselotte, hinting at Latifa’s dark past.

“Oh...”

“However, I want to do whatever I can for her. If she wants to set out into the outside world, then I want to support her. I wouldn’t have any objection to introducing you to her. That’s why I should be the one asking you—please meet with my little sister? I’m sure she’ll be delighted.” Rio quietly bowed his head.

“I understand... In that case, leave all the arrangements to me. I’d love to meet her as well. I’ll prepare a venue where she’ll be comfortable. I’ll also make sure her name and face aren’t revealed to outside parties,” Liselotte nodded firmly, taking on the role of the organizer.

“That would be very reassuring. Like I just mentioned, I especially want to keep her away from the nobles of Beltrum Kingdom. At least, as long as she doesn’t want something to the contrary...” Rio said with a slightly troubled look, his words carrying deeper meaning.

A shadow fell over Liselotte’s face. “Whatever happened must have been terrible...”

“Yes. I can’t say anything, which I am sincerely sorry for... I shall discuss things with her regarding that first, so that she can explain things to you herself if she ends up meeting you in the future.”

“I understand. Then let’s limit the participants to Satsuki, your sister, and your friends. That way the only people she would be meeting for the first time are Satsuki and myself.”

“Regarding that...” Rio fell silent for a moment, before resolutely speaking. “There’s something I must inform you. It was rather difficult to tell you before, but I believe it is the right thing to do now that we’re holding a dinner. If possible, I’d like to keep it between ourselves.”

“Of course. What is it?”

“My friends and Satsuki have already met.”

Liselotte looked clearly confused. “Umm... Was there a chance for that to happen somewhere?”

“Yes. Secretly.”

“Secretly... So His Majesty was unaware...?”

“He is unaware of this fact.”

“Then... When? How did they meet?”

“They met while we were in the capital for the banquet. It was outside of the castle. We snuck out without anyone noticing.”

“H-How...?”

“By flying.”

“I... I see.” Liselotte looked fairly shaken, but accepted his words as reality.

“I’m sure you’re surprised, but you seem to have accepted it rather easily despite that.”

Flying out of the castle was a concept so ridiculous, it would normally be dismissed immediately. It might have been possible if they had left riding griffins, but that wasn’t recommended at night and could catch the attention of the guards with the sound of their wings.

“I heard that you used your enchanted sword to fly when you rescued Lady Miharu from the enchanted ship last time.”

“So you knew already...”

“Yes. Although I didn’t expect you to sneak out of the castle.”

“My apologies. I attended through your invitation, yet behaved in such a risky manner.” Rio bowed his head in such a way as though it was being sucked downwards by gravity.

“No, I have a guess as to why you did it... But why did you reveal this to me?” Liselotte asked, looking at Rio’s face.

“Neither I nor the others are particularly skillful people. I don’t believe we would have been able to lie to the face of someone we had grown friendly with.”

Liselotte paused in wonder. “Thank you very much...” she said somewhat shyly.

“Why are you thanking me?” Rio blinked.

“I’m just happy to be told that to my face... At any rate, I’m now aware of the situation. If that’s the case, how about we hold it in my house in Amande?”

“At your estate? Satsuki will be there, right?”

He couldn’t bring her out of the castle by flying like last time, and Amande was too far away from the capital. They would definitely notice if she went missing, he thought.

“We can’t have you bring her by flying again, no? I intend on going through the proper route of asking His Majesty for permission to invite her over.”

“I see, in that case... Is it possible?”

“There’s a good chance it could happen.”

“If you say so, then it must be a fact. Can I leave it in your hands? I’ll need to let the others know.”

“Yes, you can count on me. Do you have a preferred time as to when we should hold it?”

“If you can host it within the next month or two, I’ll arrange things on my end. Any longer and I may need to travel again, however...”

“Then I’d better make a move before you need to leave again. I just so happen to plan on going to the capital next to make my report on this incident, so we may be holding it sooner than expected. I know you’ll be heading to Rodania after this, but what will you do afterwards?”

Liselotte wondered if he would stay in Rodania, or if he would accompany her to the Galarc Kingdom’s capital.

“I don’t have any plans of staying in Rodania in the long term, but Celia... I plan on leaving after I’ve confirmed her safety, as I owe her a lot,” Rio answered. Though she hadn’t said so out loud, Celia would surely remain in Rodania. It was a little sad to think they couldn’t live together anymore, but there was nothing they could do about it. Celia was a noble of Beltrum, after all.

While part of him wanted nothing more than to head for the Proxia Empire right away, he had to take some time and make sure there were no problems regarding Celia’s circumstances. That’s why he had no intention of rushing out of Rodania.

The fact he calls her name without a title means they’re fairly close, right? I wonder what kind of relationship Sir Haruto and Lady Celia have...

Liselotte was curious about it, but it wasn’t good to pry into things purely out of curiosity. And so, she exercised her self-control.

“I see...” Liselotte responded, though she still had a curious look in her eye.

“Aishia’s also looking after Miharu and my sister at the moment, so I’ll have to meet them to tell them about the dinner. But it would be best if that waited until after I meet you either in Amande or Galtuuk so that I can confirm the details of the dinner with you. You can decide the date based on what suits you and Satsuki.”

“By the way, if you were to bring Lady Miharu to Amande right now, how many days would it take?”

“If we walk normally it could take one to two weeks depending on the weather, but if I carry her while I run, we could arrive in two or three days.”

“What a wonderful time reduction... Out of curiosity, but how many days would it take you to travel from Amande to Galtuuk?”

“If I’m alone? Two days.” His fastest time would actually be if he flew, but—

“T-Two?!” It seemed that to Liselotte, even two days was plenty of a surprise.

“As you know, I can use my enchanted sword to fly. As long as I’m not hindered by bad weather, I can reduce my travel time dramatically.”

That was why the number he had given accounted for the weather. The Wilderness had especially abnormal weather, so it wasn’t rare for him to spend some days safely waiting out the weather in the stone house.

“Then... Let’s say it’ll be some time between three weeks to two months from now. Would that work for you?”

“That won’t be a problem.”

“Then I shall move ahead and presume the dinner will take place in that time frame. If transporting the ingredients is too much of an effort, I can prepare an enchanted ship depending on your location...” Liselotte hummed.

“There’s no need for that.” Rio shook his head, then looked thoughtful. “Hmm... I should inform you about this as well.”

“What is it?”

“A method of transporting items. If we’re going to be trading alcohol with each other in the future, it would be best to clarify this. Only those close to me know about this, but I trust you would be able to keep this a secret.”

“I’m quite honored you think so, but...”

Just how was he transporting things?

“This is what I use. Dissolvo.”

Rio extended the hand that held the Time-Space Cache and recited the spell. The space around his wrist warped and a ceramic bottle appeared.

“Wh... What is that?” Liselotte froze with her eyes wide open, barely managing to get her question out.

“It’s an ancient artifact called the Time-Space Cache. There are certain limitations to its use, but it can store things in a subspace isolated from time and space. As you can see, you can take items out whenever you need them,” Rio explained.

His disclosure of the magic artifact’s existence to Liselotte wasn’t a completely impulsive idea—he had been considering doing so since they signed a contract during the banquet for Liselotte to sell Rio’s homemade alcohol. This was a good opportunity to reveal it.

“An ancient artifact that can store items in a subspace isolated from time and space... Based on that information, it sounds like you can store food without it rotting?” Liselotte asked cautiously, unable to believe what she was hearing.

“Yes, that is correct.”

Liselotte’s voice audibly shook with surprise. “That is quite an unbelievable item you have there...”

An enchanted sword that could control wind, artifacts that could change hair color, and high-grade sake that could make a noble groan with a single sip... Just how many treasures did he have hidden? She was starting to feel more exasperated than impressed at this point.

Possessing this many impressive goods was abnormal in itself, yet because she was aware of Rio’s irregular strength, even this abnormality was faint in comparison.

An artifact that can transport goods without taking up space?! I want it! I want it so badly! But I can’t say such unreasonable things to Sir Haruto!

The Time-Space Cache was an item any merchant would kill for. Liselotte nearly blurted for him to give it to her, but swallowed her words with difficulty. Because it was an ancient magic artifact, it was probably impossible to manufacture or acquire.

“There’s alcohol in this bottle, if you’d like to have it.” Rio placed the sake bottle on the table as an offering.

“W-Why, thank you very much.” Liselotte bowed her head.

“And so, I’m able to transport goods using this artifact. There’s no need to worry.”

“I understand.” Liselotte smiled wryly, accepting that her worries were needless.

“Also, Dissolvo.” Rio held his hand out over the table and recited the spell once again. A plate of finely cut chocolate appeared. “This is Miharu’s homemade chocolate.”

“Miharu’s...” Liselotte gulped. Unfortunately, there were no snacks in this room, and the only thing on the table was their tea. This would be the perfect snack to go alone with it.

“You chant Conditum to put it away,” Rio said flatly, storing the chocolate plate back inside the Time-Space Cache.

“Ah...” Liselotte let out a half-surprised, half-disappointed sound.

“Dissolvo. Please have it with your tea, if you’d like,” Rio chuckled as he brought out the plate again. He had only put it away as a demonstration of the artifact’s effect—he intended on giving her the chocolate from the start.

“T-Then, I shall gratefully accept one...” Liselotte shyly reached for the plate of chocolate. Knowing how delicious Miharu’s homemade sweets were, she couldn’t resist. “I-It’s so good!”

Rio also reached for one so that Liselotte wouldn’t feel self-conscious while she ate. A sweet but not-too-thick flavor spread in his mouth.

“It’s delicious,” Rio commented.

“Mmm!” A sound of joy slipped out from Liselotte, who nodded enthusiastically as she beamed. Her lovely reaction made Rio smile softly.

“Come to think of it, you said you had something you wanted to discuss too?”

“I wanted to ask you about the two Japanese boys that traveled with you. I don’t know if they’ve realized it yet, but the moment they hear the names of Ricca Guild’s products, they’ll notice the use of Earth words in the product names.”

In order to prepare for that, she wanted to know what kind of people they were like. Once Liselotte answered Rio’s question, she lifted her teacup in a picture-perfect show of etiquette.

“I see... It hasn’t been that long since I’ve met them myself, but I don’t think either of them are bad people. Kouta is a honest person with a strong sense of justice, and Rei can be a little silly at times, but he watches his surroundings carefully and is always considerate of Kouta. The only thing you have to be wary of is that the two of them are completely normal Japanese high school students, so they’re not really familiar with this world...”

Perhaps that was why Rui was so worried about Kouta and Rei, Rio thought.

“Do you know what they plan on doing after this?”

“I don’t think either of them have decided yet. But it’s very likely they’ll end up joining the Restoration, I believe...” Rio answered, thinking back to how their conversation with Rui made it seem like they left the castle in a spur of the moment decision. Christina had also said they were stowaways on the enchanted ship.

“I understand. Thank you for telling me this.”

“I hope it helped.”

“Yes. I have no intention of telling them about my past life for now, but depending on how it goes in the future, I may reveal things to them.”

They had only just met, so this was probably the most appropriate decision.

“Out of curiosity, how would you have explained your company’s secret if someone untrustworthy asks about the products?” Rio inquired with interest.

“The explanation I have prepared is that the production method was recorded in ancient documents that were discovered. I’ve also prepared those documents.”

“You’ve covered it all.”

Since there were Japanese people who had transferred into this world in the present, it wouldn’t be a stretch to think similar people had done so in the past.

“It was a huge pain to create, though.” Liselotte smiled bitterly, recalling how she made the documents. She couldn’t let anyone realize the handwriting was her own, so she had Aria pen the documents on her behalf, but it took quite some time to make it look convincing.

“Would you like me to indirectly mention that to the two of them?” Rio suggested.

“I appreciate the concern, but I want to try talking to them myself. I’ll see if I can arrange some time to have a chat with them,” Liselotte shook her head, turning down Rio’s offer. After that, they continued their conversation for a little longer.

◇　◇　◇

A few minutes later, they finished their chat and Rio left the room to find Cosette and Chloe waiting in front of Liselotte’s room.

“Hello, the two of you are here as well?” he called out to them.

“Good day, Sir Haruto. We were waiting for you. None of us recalled showing you to your room and we couldn’t find you anywhere in the fortress, so we were wondering if you were with our master,” Cosette answered with a cheerful grin pasted on her face.

Why was Sir Haruto in Lady Liselotte’s room? With just the two of them. She looked at her master with an expression of protest.

“Oh, good timing. Chloe, show Sir Haruto to his room,” Liselotte said, smoothly ignoring Cosette’s gaze.

“Yes, ma’am. Sir Haruto, please come this way.” Chloe immediately moved, inviting Rio along.

“Well then. Liselotte, Cosette, please excuse me here.” Rio gave his farewells without realizing the exchange going on behind the smiles of the master and attendant.

“Please enjoy your time here and rest,” Liselotte replied with a bright expression. Then, as soon as Rio and Chloe disappeared down the corridor and out of sight—

“Hey, why didn’t you let me show Sir Haruto the way? And more importantly, why were you two meeting alone? In Lady Liselotte’s room, no less,” Cosette protested.

“There weren’t enough people, so I simply dealt with it accordingly. I also had something to discuss with him. You knew that too, which is why you were waiting in front of my room, no?”

“Hmph. Still, inviting someone into the room of a high-ranked noblewoman with no attendants around is a clear display of favor towards them. Why haven’t I heard that you have Sir Haruto in your sights? That means I have no hope!”

“I don’t recall saying that I liked Sir Haruto in that way, though.” Liselotte’s reply was nonchalant, as if to say that she shouldn’t misunderstand.

I wonder if it’s even being conveyed... My favor? she questioned, evading Cosette’s gaze. She had been raised with zero experience in love in both her previous and present life, so she lacked knowledge in that area.

“I know you don’t recall saying it. We don’t recall hearing it either, after all. The problem is whether you favor him or not,” Cosette pressed Liselotte forcefully.

“Enough of this—we’re going. I want to see the two boys that arrived with Sir Haruto. You—come along.” Liselotte started walking briskly, a faint blush on her cheeks. Cosette puffed up her cheeks with a “Hmph!” and followed after her.

◇　◇　◇

Around the time Rio arrived at Liselotte’s room, Christina and Duke Huguenot were meeting in a drawing room.

For Charles and Sir Emarle to be taken prisoner... Princess Christina sure obtained some outrageous souvenirs. Princess Flora is easier to deal with, and the way she sits still without moving is truly convenient, but... Her demerits have enough merits to overlook. The problem is the amount of power she’s given, Duke Huguenot thought in the time before the conversation started.

“I shall now excuse myself here. If you need anything, I will be waiting outside the room.”

Natalie had been preparing tea for them, but she naturally couldn’t stay and listen to the conversation between two foreign nobles, so she voluntarily exited the room. This left Christina and Duke Huguenot alone to finally start their conversation.

“If I may express my amazement, Your Highness: for Charles Arbor and Sir Alfred to both be captured as prisoners... It’s a splendid feat,” Duke Huguenot said as soon as the door closed.

“The one who apprehended them was Sir Amakawa, not myself,” Christina replied coolly.

“However, getting acquainted with him and tasking him with your safety was all Your Highness’ skill. I thought it was such a shame that the Galarc Kingdom acquired him already, but then Your Highness brought him out as a trump card. And I hear the three other girls are also skilled enchanted sword wielders? Celia is the genius sorcerer from our kingdom, too. There’d be nothing more delightful than to have them all join the Restoration, wouldn’t you say?” Duke Huguenot raised both his arms.

The Restoration had been concerned by their lack of reliable personnel who were skilled in combat and sorcery. If that insufficiency could be amended in a single go, he would have no choice but to welcome them all wholeheartedly, even though Christina had the potential of becoming a thorn in his side.

“It’s still too early to say that. Professor Celia aside, Sir Amakawa and the other three girls are not nobles of the Beltrum Kingdom. I am indebted to them, but they are still outsiders. There’s no guarantee they will continue cooperating with the Restoration in the future. You shouldn’t assume otherwise,” Christina warned stiffly.

“However... Didn’t Sir Amakawa kidnap Celia from the ceremony in order to strike a blow to the Arbor faction’s influence and serve in guarding Your Highness?”

They must have had some political interest in common for him to have offered his support, and so there should be a way to continue receiving his support, Duke Huguenot implied in his question.

“The common interest that made Sir Amakawa and the girls cooperate with us is unrelated to our goal of reducing the Arbor faction’s power.”

“By which you mean...?”

Christina hesitated, wondering if she should stay quiet about Haruto and Celia’s relationship, but realized the way they interacted with each other made it fairly obvious. With that thought, she decided to say it—it also made her story coherent and served as a warning. “Professor Celia’s rescue.”

“I could tell Celia and Sir Amakawa are close by watching them, but what exactly is their relationship?”

“Professor Celia is Sir Amakawa’s savior. Although, it seems that now she is the one feeling more indebted to him.”

“Well, it would be difficult to repay a debt as large as Sir Amakawa’s achievements... However, he isn’t the kind of person to think his debt is repaid so easily, is he?” Duke Huguenot asked, implying that this was their chance to get him on their side.

“Right... That’s why there’s no way he’d oppose us as long as Professor Celia joins the Restoration. But if we ever harmed her in any way, that sword of his would be pointed right at us without a hint of mercy,” Christina cut in sharply.

“Of course, we have no intention of harming Celia...” Duke Huguenot shrugged his shoulders with a nihilistic smile.

“Naturally. But there’s no guarantee that someone else in the Restoration won’t harass Professor Celia in order to gain Sir Amakawa’s cooperation, is there?”

“We wouldn’t allow something like that, but...” Duke Huguenot didn’t deny the possibility.

“You need to keep a thoroughly watchful eye on things, so that no such fools appear. Professor Celia will be under my protection hereafter, so I will be merciless in my judgments against anything strange.”

Whether that was an order or a warning was unclear.

“That sounds rather overprotective. Will you be giving Celia your patronage, then?” Duke Huguenot asked jokingly.

“Isn’t that a given? Sir Amakawa easily brushed aside the elite squad of knights and sorcerers that Charles led, shut down Alfred and Sir Shigekura in a head-on fight, and made 5,000 soldiers tremble in fear. It would be best to keep a favorable relationship with someone like that. Which is why Professor Celia will be the most important person in our connection to Sir Amakawa. I thought you would have understood this much.”

“I am aware of this, but I know many are anticipating Sir Amakawa’s assistance as well. In my humble opinion, we should be pursuing a favorable relationship more proactively...”

“I agree... That’s why I won’t go as far as to say that we should give up. However, I can’t approve of persistent attempts to solicit him when he isn’t interested. This is a matter of showing Sir Amakawa our good faith in order to win over as much of his trust as we can. That’s why I’ll say this again: you need to watch that no such fools appear,” Christina said, strongly emphasizing her point.

“Understood. Being too persistent and creating animosity would indeed be a foolish plan. For the time being, I shall keep it at an invitation to Rodania and a seat at the celebration.” Duke Huguenot placed his hand on his chest and nodded respectfully.

That’s quite some enthusiasm on her part, but I understand her reasoning. He defeated a hero—one of the living legends in this world—and Sir Emarle, Beltrum’s strongest. Possibly Strahl’s strongest. His achievements this time will raise his name even further... He’s a piece that I want to obtain no matter what.

Duke Huguenot thought to himself with his face ducked down. However, he understood that using forceful methods against Haruto, who was currently as famous as a hero, would be a bad move. He was a desirable combat force, and Duke Huguenot would have all the options in the world if Flora had been the one opposing him, but he couldn’t take such risks against Christina.

I wonder what kind of face this man would make if he knew the incident his son made a mess of was what drove such a person out of the Beltrum Kingdom? And how would he move afterwards...? No, there’s no proof Sir Haruto is the same person. There’s no point in thinking about it, Christina thought, then immediately erased those thoughts herself.

This much warning should be enough to hold Duke Huguenot back. All that’s left is Flora. Perhaps she...

There were several things about the earlier discussion that bothered Christina—she’d have to confirm them later. She ended that train of thought there and returned her focus to the person sitting opposite her. There were still things she needed to ask.

“In addition to this, I’d like to hear about the events that occurred while I was away.”

“Why, the most notable event would be Your Highness’s arrival with Charles Arbor in tow as prisoner, but...” Duke Huguenot placed a hand over his mouth in thought. “First, as I’m sure you’ve heard already, Princess Flora was kidnapped by a man named Lucius in Amande. And...” He stared closely at Christina’s face.

I heard about that from Sir Amakawa on the way here, but I’ll ask Flora for the details later.

“And? What else?” Christina asked while concurrently thinking to herself.

“Princess Flora and Sir Hiroaki are now engaged.”

Christina’s expression flickered. “...What did you just say?”

“After the banquet, marriage offers for Sir Hiroaki increased rapidly. This was decided just the other day, when we decided that it would be bad to prolong the decision of Sir Hiroaki’s first wife. Sir Hiroaki and Princess Flora have both given their agreement, and King Francois of Galarc has been informed,” Duke Huguenot reported eloquently.

“Has it been announced publicly?” Christina asked in a stiff voice.

“No. It hasn’t been announced yet, and not even Liselotte should be aware of it yet. The plan was to make the announcement upon arriving back in Rodania.”

“...” Christina fell silent. Political marriages were the natural duty of women in royalty and nobility, but marriage was still too early for Flora. That’s what her heart was telling her, but was she just being a needlessly worried sister?

Flora surely didn’t have any other choice. She must have accepted the engagement prepared for her without knowing anything about what marriage involved.

“Is there anything problematic about it?” Duke Huguenot asked innocently. With Hiroaki’s agreement and Francois’ knowledge about the engagement, not even the First Princess Christina could make an objection so easily. The duke was asking this while knowing that. Besides, it was only logical to offer something commensurate when trying to obtain beneficial personnel.

If Princess Flora and Sir Hiroaki’s engagement works out, it’ll make it easier for me to intervene. It was worth rushing the engagement.

Duke Huguenot chuckled amiably.

“...No, I was just a little surprised.” Christina shook her head with the utmost calmness. There was no telling what Hiroaki would hear if she got emotional and said the wrong thing here. That’s why she had no other choice right now.

If only... If only I had come a bit sooner...

She would have been able to take her place. She would have been able to lighten Flora’s burden. Christina cursed her own helplessness from the bottom of her heart.

◇　◇　◇

Meanwhile, in the meeting room beside Christina and Duke Huguenot, Celia and Aria were holding their long awaited reunion.

“I feared for you when you were abducted from your wedding ceremony, but I’m so glad to see you safe and sound. Though I never imagined we would reunite in such a way... No, I suppose it would be more accurate to say we’ve already?” Aria smiled.

“Ahaha... I couldn’t reveal myself as Celia Claire to anyone at the time. I’m sorry,” Celia apologized, feeling ashamed for deceiving her old friend.

“There’s no need to apologize. If anything, I should be the one thanking you. You helped Amande when we were being attacked even at the risk of revealing yourself.”

“I only did what was right. And the one who decided to help was Haruto. You should thank him, not me.”

“Sir Amakawa isn’t someone I can casually request a meeting with, but if I ever have a chance to speak with him privately I shall do exactly that.” Aria nodded her head deeply, agreeing.

“Ah, right... He’s really that remarkable now. Then I’ll mention it to him too,” Celia mumbled earnestly, pressing her hand against her chin in thought. Then she giggled as though she felt pride in that fact.

“Yes, please do... You know, you look really happy when you talk about him,” Aria pointed out with a chuckle.

“R... Really?” Celia was taken aback, blushing faintly.

“Are you unaware of it?”

“I-I’m the same as always. Totally normal. It’s only natural to be happy when someone close to you is being acknowledged.” Celia feigned a prim face as she spoke to a somewhat exasperated Aria.

“If I may be so bold to ask... Are you and Sir Amakawa in love with each other?”

“I-In love?!” Celia suddenly turned bright red.

“It seems complicated circumstances are involved in the sequence of events where Sir Amakawa saved you, so naturally, there’s no need to answer if you cannot. However, as an old friend, I cannot help but feel curious about those circumstances.”

“H-Haruto and I aren’t like that, we’re not in love or anything...” Celia said, trailing off in embarrassment.

“I see. His feelings aside, it seems you have feelings for him.”

“I said you’re wrong!”

“Right, right,” Aria chuckled in understanding.

Chapter 3: Jealousy

Around the time Rio was finishing up his discussion with Liselotte, Hiroaki had been led to a guest room by Cosette and invited Flora and Roanna inside to soothe his boredom.

Generally, Roanna would bring up a topic, Hiroaki would rattle on about it, Roanna would ask a question that was easy for Hiroaki to answer with a boast, and Hiroaki would continue the conversation from there. Roanna was a responsive conversation partner that reacted in a way that made the speaker feel good, so she truly was a comfortable person for Hiroaki to converse with.

“I used to think my sense of personal space was on the bigger side, but I guess you never really know,” Hiroaki said while sitting down on the narrow three-seater sofa. Flora and Roanna sat on either side of him while he had his arms spread.

Normally, they would either all sit on individual sofas or comfortably share a three-seater between two of them while the third sat on an individual sofa, but the guest rooms in the fortress only had the bare minimum in the way of furnishings.

“Well, sit down,” Hiroaki had said, having positioned himself in the center of the sofa and beckoned Flora and Roanna over, resulting in the three of them sitting together.

“Personal space?” Roanna reacted to Hiroaki’s words, inclining her head.

“Ah, it’s the distance where other people are too close for comfort. The closer you are to the other person, the shorter this distance is, and the less acquainted you are, the wider it is. You wouldn’t want to sit here with a random old man, right?”

“Indeed, I would prefer to decline such a thing... But I have no opposition to the current arrangement,” Roanna said, bringing herself closer to Hiroaki’s shoulder. Meanwhile, Flora maintained a shy distance that avoided contact with Hiroaki’s body.

“My personal space used to be so big, I found it annoying when someone entered an empty restaurant after me and sat themselves within my field of view. But I don’t dislike the current setup,” Hiroaki snorted, grabbing Roanna’s shoulder and holding her closer.

“Geez, that was because it was a man, wasn’t it?” Roanna asked with a cute pout.

“Nah, there are some times where I hate it because it’s a woman, too. Especially when there are other open seats, but they purposefully sit near me. I just want to eat my food in peace, but they start blabbering about dumb topics.”

“What do you mean by that...?”

One might think she was asking if he didn’t like her sticking so close at the moment.

“I wonder?” Hiroaki smirked, evading Roanna’s stare with a laugh. At that moment, he could tell Roanna pressed herself even closer. He chuckled smugly. “It’s a narrow seat, but things like this are nice every once in a while too, no?”

“I don’t mind if we’re like this all the time, though,” Roanna answered with a slight pout.

“Hahaha!” Hiroaki burst into hearty laughter. Then he sighed and said, “Ah, it really is the best to have someone who understands you when you’re tired and feeling frayed along the edges. In reality, being with women who are all looks and zero understanding is so irritating.”

The ones who came to mind were the girls who weren’t in this room right now—with the exception of Christina. He was displeased with the fact they hadn’t actively tried to involve themselves with him, the hero. Just recalling it made his irritation return.

“I guess that means I’m an understanding woman, then?” Roanna immediately asked.

“Nope,” Hiroaki shook his head. Then, he added, “You’re understanding and you have the looks. A truly charming lady indeed.”

“Geez,” Roanna blushed in embarrassment.

“So, what’s with you, Flora? You’ve been silent this entire time.” Satisfied with Roanna’s reaction, Hiroaki turned to Flora, who hadn’t participated in the conversation at all.

“Huh...? Ah... No...” Flora was unable to come up with any words at the moment. She seemed distracted, like her mind simply wasn’t there.

“...” Hiroaki sighed disapprovingly.

“Umm, I was thinking about my sister and Sir Haruto... I was wondering what they were up to,” Flora answered with naive honesty.

“Who knows? Christina should be talking to Duke Huguenot, right? But why bring up his name?” Hiroaki frowned openly at the mention of Haruto’s name. Not again, he thought.

“No, I was just thinking that a lot must have happened while they were traveling.”

“Between Christina and that bastard?”

“That’s not what I mean, but Professor Celia was there too...” Flora trailed off.

“Hmm...” With even Celia’s name mentioned, Hiroaki hummed with disinterest. But on the inside, his displeasure was rapidly building. “Is it really a big deal? That he defeated the King’s Sword or whatever? It seemed like people were making a rather big fuss about it,” he said, expressing his doubts towards Alfred’s abilities.

“Sir Emarle has been acknowledged by the king as Beltrum’s strongest. He can use an enchanted sword to release powerful blades of light, and his strength is so well known that they say it’s an understatement to call him a one-man army,” Roanna said a little hesitantly, knowing that the answer wasn’t what Hiroaki wanted to hear.

“Yet he and that Rui bastard were beaten up by that fresh-off-the-farm greenhorn. That Rui bastard—it impacts me too if he loses in a way that sullies the name of heroes,” Hiroaki mumbled sullenly.

So the King’s Sword uses blades of lights to attack? Sounds like setting off my Divine Arms at full power would definitely be stronger. But Satsuki already lost to him in a sparring match, and that Takahisa bastard also had a bad time against him. He appeared around the same time as the heroes, yet he’s standing out more than us. At this rate, he’ll be valued higher than us. Even his name is similar to us Japanese people.

If only there was something he could do about it, he thought as he felt a sense of danger from Haruto’s recent activities.

Hmm. Is there anything I can do to lower that bastard’s protagonist characterization? By making him lose face or something...

He folded his arms in discontent, falling silent in thought. Meanwhile, Roanna sensed his mood and quietly waited for Hiroaki to begin speaking again, while Flora awkwardly remained silent.

It’d be so convenient if someone could just go and defeat him once. Seeing how the so-called kingdom’s strongest—the King’s Sword—was no match for him, no one in the Restoration will be able to beat him in a close-ranged match either...

Everyone was just so worthless: all name and no substance. There wasn’t anyone who was the “real deal,” as it were. However, though he was irritating, Haruto Amakawa’s abilities were probably real. Hiroaki had witnessed Haruto fight in the flesh from up close, and his combat powers were indeed impressive. He didn’t want to admit it, but Haruto was strong. However...

Hold on a minute... There’s no need to fight in a close ranged battle where the bastard has the upper hand, is there? If I can maintain a distance while one-sidedly attacking him, then...

A brilliant idea suddenly came to Hiroaki’s mind.

That’s right—fighting in his ring would be nonsense. That fool Rui also went out of his way to fight him at close range when he’s a bow user, or so I hear. That was probably why he lost. He should have just camped somewhere advantageous and defeated him with long-ranged attacks.

Hiroaki analyzed the cause of Rui’s defeat and sneered.

Dragging your opponent into your own ring to win is the ultimate tactic. Since the power I obtained is too great even in an incomplete form, I’ve rarely had the chance to test it out properly, but wouldn’t he be the perfect opponent? If I say I want to test my ability, it might work.

He could see a way for him to win against Haruto Amakawa. Of course, it would be a sparring match, so they wouldn’t fight for real, but it would be a good form of stress relief. There was no telling if Haruto would agree to the match, but it wouldn’t hurt to ask.

Ah, great. In the end, I have to be the one standing out.

The only ones who could cull the genuinely strong were the stronger.

“Ah, I’ve just thought of something. I’m going to see Haruto.”

Hiroaki immediately began his plan.

◇　◇　◇

Around the same time, Chloe was leading Rio to his guest room after his discussion with Liselotte ended.

“Here you go—please use this room. This is the key,” Chloe said, stopping in front of the room and handing Rio the key.

“Thank you very much, Chloe. If you don’t mind me asking, where are Sara and the girls who came together with me?” Rio asked.

“I showed them to their room right over there.” Chloe gestured with her right hand, pointing out the room where Sara and the others were staying.

“I understand. If you would excuse me,” Rio said, then started walking towards Sara’s room.

“Sure.”

I wonder what kind of relationship he has with the three of them? Chloe wondered, watching Rio knock on the door before she left. The door opened and Sara stuck her head out from within.

“Haruto.”

“Sorry to keep you waiting.”

“Not at all. Please, come inside.”

After that exchange, Rio entered the room as Chloe quietly left.

“Pardon the intrusion,” Rio said as he stepped inside.

“We were waiting.”

“You’ve worked hard today.”

Orphia and Alma welcomed Rio from where they sat on the beds.

“Please, have a seat.”

“Thanks.” Rio sat down on one side of the three-seater sofa that Sara offered him.

“There was something we had to tell you, Rio.” Sara used Rio’s real name since only those in the know were in the room.

“What is it?”

“Now that Princess Christina has joined up with her allies, we were thinking of returning to the stone house. We don’t think we should get too deeply involved with the noble class of humans—or human politics in general,” Sara began.

“I see... I agree, that would probably be for the best.”

The spirit folk girls were eye-catching enough with their appearances, but they must have attracted a lot of attention by showing up in a group while wielding enchanted swords. If they continued to Rodania like this, they would definitely receive some form of invitation.

“We do want to continue accompanying you, but...” Sara said worriedly. Orphia and Alma frowned too.

“No, you’ve been a tremendous help coming this far. The journey will shift to enchanted ships once we reach Amande, so you’ve done enough. I’d appreciate it if you could protect Miharu and Latifa instead.”

“Of course!” The girls nodded energetically in unison.

In contrast, Rio had a shadow over his face. “Thank you so much. And I have to apologize for how much danger you were subjected to. Especially to you, Orphia—you were injured as a result.”

“What are you saying? Celia isn’t important to just you, Haruto. She’s important to us as well,” Sara said.

“Yes, exactly,” Alma agreed.

“We’ve all recovered completely and nothing terrible happened. We were all really happy to be able to travel around and learn about the world with you. We’ve never had the chance to travel on foot before, so everything felt new,” Orphia said, flashing a bashful smile.

“You even got Rio to hold you in a bridal carry at the end there.”

“That’s right... Wait! What are you saying, Alma?!” Orphia protested with a faint blush.

Sara watched the two of them and sighed. “We learned a lot from this trip, especially in that final fight with the mercenaries. If you hadn’t taught us how to fight against people, we may have had a much tougher time,” she said, looking back on the battle.

“Indeed. It was great that we were able to get real experience fighting.”

“Yup. And now we know there are lots of strong humans out there, too. The one I went up against was especially tough.”

Alma and Orphia added to Sara’s words with serious expressions.

“The King’s Sword... Was what they called him, right? From what I saw of Rio’s battle, we wouldn’t be able to win against him—not with the limitation of fighting while we pretended our weapons were catalysts for sorcery activation, at least,” Sara analyzed with a stern look.

“However, if you were able to use your spirit arts freely, warriors as skilled as yourselves should be able to hold your own. If things ever get really dangerous, please don’t hesitate to fight using your spirit arts. I do not wish to see anyone else getting hurt from fighting,” Rio requested with a worried face. He had been beside himself with worry when he had arrived to see Orphia and Celia down on the ground before Charles and the others. The village had placed a rule on them to keep their species and spirit arts hidden as much as possible when they departed, but it wasn’t something they needed to worry about protecting at the cost of their lives. At least, that was what Rio believed.

“Thank you very much...” Sara and the others exchanged looks before thanking him with embarrassed joy. They could tell Rio was truly worried about them.

“There’s nothing you should be thanking me for...” Rio said with a pained smile.

“I’m happy that you were angry on behalf of Celia and myself,” Orphia said, closing her eyes and placing a hand over her healed stomach.

“...It was the right thing to do,” Rio said awkwardly. If possible, he didn’t want others to see him being angry and acting violently, since he normally gave off an image of rationality and humanity. He had previously scared Ruri and Sayo like that, too.

“We saw you in a way we’d never imagined before, but it was a really cool version of you, you know?” Orphia said with a grin, staring at Rio’s face.

“Please don’t make fun of me...” Rio’s eyes widened faintly before he ducked his face. He was smiling softly in embarrassment.

“Orphia’s right. It reminded me of when you protected Latifa when the wyvern flock attacked the village,” Alma agreed with a giggle.

“I remember that,” Sara said, keenly recalling those memories.

“It was a long time ago now.”

“It’s been four or five years since then.”

Orphia and Alma reminisced with distant looks in their eyes. Perhaps that was why the room filled with pensive silence.

“Come to think of it, what were you discussing with Liselotte?” Sara asked, changing the topic.

“We were making plans for next month. Liselotte was thinking of bringing Satsuki to her home and hosting a meal, and invited me to attend with everyone in the stone house...” Rio said.

“Oh. We’d love to attend, but...”

“We just decided it would be best for us not to get involved with human nobility and politics.”

Sara and the others were rather attracted to the offer. The amount of politics involved in attending Liselotte’s personally hosted meal was completely different to the act of going to Rodania, but the fact they were contradicting themselves already was apparent. If he had asked at a later time, they may have answered differently, but...

“What do we do?” Alma asked Sara and Orphia.

“We’ll pass this time. Even though having a meal together shouldn’t have any political impact, creating exceptions so easily could lead to a slippery slope of making more exceptions in the future...” Sara declared regretfully, her tone extremely serious.

“It’s too bad, but you’re right,” Orphia agreed.

“There’s nothing we can do about it,” Alma shrugged sadly.

“However, since we’re passing this time, we’ll definitely participate next time! If there’s a next time! Definitely!” Sara said, adding a condition to their refusal.

“Doesn’t that defeat the point?” Alma laughed at Sara.

“It’s fine! We have to demonstrate our self-control here, so that the next time we can reward ourselves for doing so,” Sara said, turning away in a huff.

“Right,” Orphia giggled.

“Ah, but Latifa can go ahead and attend. She’ll probably be sulking when we return to the stone house anyway, saying we got to have all the fun. It’ll be a good social experience for her to meet Liselotte,” Sara added.

“I understand. I’m sure Latifa will be delighted as well. I’ll pass on what you’ve said to Liselotte about your attendance, too,” Rio nodded with a gentle expression.

Just then, a knocking sound came from the door.

“Was that a knock...?”

Everyone’s attention gathered on the door.

“Maybe it’s Celia?” Sara stood up and walked over to the door, opening it with a clack.

“’Sup!” The door opened to reveal Hiroaki, standing there with Flora and Roanna.

“The hero, Princess Flora, and Lady Roanna...” Rio immediately stood up, eyes widening in surprise as he greeted the three of them.

“Hello...” Sara met Hiroaki’s eyes and nodded her head in greeting.

“Sorry to disturb you in the middle of your fun—I heard from this lady that you were in this room,” Hiroaki looked around and snorted. Standing on either side of him was a flustered Flora and awkward Roanna. Behind him was Chloe, who had probably led them to the room; she looked bored.

“Did you need something?” Rio asked.

“Oh, it’s nothing much. I just had a request for you, considering your abilities.”

“By which you mean...?”

“Do you want to have a mock battle with me?”

“May I inquire as to the reason why...?” Rio looked confused at the sudden challenge. He was unsure if he should readily give his consent to it.

“Well, I’m sure you’ve heard the legends of how mighty the Divine Arms the heroes possess are, but there haven’t been any opportunities for me to unleash mine at full power. It’s a bit of a nuclear weapon... Like magic capable of genocide. Using it carelessly could change the terrain of the land, causing all kinds of secondary disasters. I suppose it can’t be helped, since there’s no knowing how much damage might occur, but if I don’t practice fighting while drawing out its power to some extent, I might not be able to control myself when the time comes, you know?” Hiroaki lamented with a sigh, stating his perfectly reasoned argument.

“Well, I suppose,” Rio said in a dull tone, still unable to read Hiroaki’s intentions. The statement wasn’t entirely incorrect, but it had come too quickly out of the blue.

“But if I fight with my Divine Arm’s abilities activated, even in a mock battle, the average person is unfit to be my opponent. Even if I have no intention of killing them, I fear they’ll be unable to evade my attacks and die on me. I need to fight a warrior that’s actually strong. That’s when I realized you’d be a good opponent, since you defeated Rui and the King’s Sword. I feel bad for singling you out like this, but can I ask this of you?” Hiroaki said, then glanced over and watched for Rio’s reaction.

“Umm... I’m sorry for the unreasonable request. We haven’t consulted with my sister about it yet either, so it’s okay if you refuse him.” Flora, who had been anxiously listening to Hiroaki talk, was unable to contain herself any longer and spoke up.

“Eh?” Hiroaki let out a small noise reflexively. Flora was a coward that normally didn’t speak up, yet she had to go and do something unnecessary now. Why did she decide to speak up this time? Because it concerned Haruto? That thought agitated him.

I see. So it’s just him being selfish. Rio had thought it was strange Christina wasn’t here to begin with, but the exchange just now instantly helped him make that guess.

“I am unworthy of such high praise. However, if you wish to demonstrate the power of your Divine Arms, the time and location must be selected carefully. It is not something I can lightly accept at my own discretion. Once you obtain Princess Christina’s approval, I will gladly accept,” Rio said, cheerfully giving his consent with a condition. However, he wasn’t saying it as a diplomatic excuse to avoid causing offense through rejection—he really didn’t mind fighting as long as the conditions were met.

I may potentially fight with other heroes in the future. Rui had held back from the beginning of our fight, and I want to know more about the powers hidden within the Divine Arms.

If his opponent was willing to reveal his own hand, then it wouldn’t be a bad idea to accept this opportunity. There was no need for him to actually win, so he could fight with the abilities that people knew he had without showing off anything new. If he couldn’t win like that, that was fine.

Hiroaki seemed to be displeased by the lack of an immediate acceptance on Haruto’s part, as he looked slightly sullen, but he refrained from saying anything more, sensing that it would be too pushy to do so.

“Thank you very much. Then we shall inquire with Princess Christina.” Roanna said her thanks and promptly wrapped up the conversation. She must have disagreed with deciding this without Christina’s permission, as she looked somewhat relieved.

“Please do,” Rio bowed his head respectfully, closing the curtain on this discussion.

◇　◇　◇

Later that night, Christina summoned Rio to her, as she wished to speak to him directly. He walked to the designated meeting room to find Flora and Christina together, which made him slightly confused. There was no one else in sight.

It feels kind of strange being with these two together...

It was something that had never happened once throughout his days in the Royal Academy. The reason why he was called here was almost certainly because of the mock battle with Hiroaki, but considering the events of the past and what happened after reuniting with these two, Rio couldn’t help but feel a little awkward.

“Thank you for coming so late at night. Please, have a seat,” Christina said, politely gesturing at a chair. Rio nodded and sat down.

“Thank you.”

“I called you here because I want to discuss the mock battle with the hero. Flora said she wanted to sit in and listen too. I hope you don’t mind?” Christina asked.

“No, of course not.”

“Then, to get straight to the point—are you really okay with having the mock battle?”

“Yes. As long as Your Highness has consented, I don’t mind.” Rio nodded his head easily at Christina’s prying question.

“If you’re wary that refusing the hero will cause problems or offense, you’re allowed to decline without concern for others. I will deal with things on my end.”

The partial agreement between Rio and Hiroaki made it hard for Christina to decide whether to give her permission or not. However, it would be a different matter if Rio expressed a desire to refuse.

“I am not acting out of concern for others. If anything, I am concerned as to what Your Highness thinks. If a mock battle between Sir Hiroaki and myself would cause inconvenience for you, I will readily withdraw at your word,” Rio replied with a smile as he looked at Christina.

“The matter that worries me the most is whether this is troublesome for you. If so, I can only offer my utmost apologies.”

“It may become a problem if I receive frequent challenges to mock battles, but this one case doesn’t particularly bother me.” Rio would have preferred more thought to have gone into the timing of the request, but Christina understood that without Rio having to complain, which was why she looked so apologetic.

“And what is the next matter that worries you?” If she had a matter that worried her the most, then there must be something else, Rio thought.

“This is less of a worry and more of a request. Can you win against Sir Sakata in the mock battle?” Christina asked with a serious expression.

“I’m afraid I won’t know until we actually fight...”

Rio still didn’t know of the extent of the Divine Arms. The abilities of Satsuki and Takahisa’s Divine Arms were sealed in close combat when he had sparred with them, and Rui had been aiming to immobilize rather than kill when they were fighting. Above all, Rui had hesitated, making the bad choice of approaching Rio even though he was an archer.

Based on his experience fighting the other heroes until now, Rio didn’t think they were opponents worth fearing when brought into close-ranged combat, as they hadn’t received any combat training while in Japan. Veterans like Alfred, Gouki, or Uzuma were more formidable.

However, depending on the extent of the power within the Divine Arms, that could change. If they could maintain a distance as they attacked him freely with attacks on the level of natural disasters, then they’d be much more of a problem.

“Would it be better for me to lose the mock battle?” Rio asked. If the hero was allowed to use his abilities and seriously take him on in the mock battle, losing would be a bad look for the Restoration. That’s what Rio assumed, and why he didn’t mind losing in the first place.

“No, the opposite. If you can win, I’d like to ask that you please do.”

“Huh...?” Flora let out a sound of confusion from beside her, possibly because she hadn’t heard of this in advance.

“May I inquire as to the reason why...?” Rio asked.

“I first noticed this when we met at the banquet, but after reuniting at this fortress and speaking more, I’m now certain. The hero seems to be a little arrogant,” Christina stated plainly.

“...” It was a difficult statement to both agree and disagree with, so Rio was silent and waited.

“At any and every moment of time, he has to be treated with the highest priority. If things don’t go his way, he shows his displeasure—and it’s so obvious that everyone around him can see it. It may have been part of Duke Huguenot’s plan, but I believe he’s been spoiled a little too much in the time it took for me to reach Rodania. Of course, I cannot completely fault the plan if it was for the sake of the organization...” Christina said with difficulty. “But there’s a limit to how far you can go. I believe there are no exceptions to this, whether you are the princess of a kingdom like me, a king, or a hero. Above all, if things continue like this, neither the hero nor we will benefit from it. That’s why I believe it would be good for him to lose some of that pride of his.”

Not even royalty could speak out too strongly against heroes, said to be the embodiment of divine majesty. However, that didn’t mean they could allow his arrogance to continue unhindered.

“And your wish is that I play a role in doing just that. Is that correct?”

“It’s not a matter that can be left to the average person, and I cannot ask anyone I do not trust. No one even knows about this apart from the three of us here. I am voicing my private thoughts for the first time here.”

Which meant...

She hasn’t consulted Duke Huguenot or Roanna, then. No—Roanna aside, she couldn’t consult with Duke Huguenot. Their plans oppose each other.

Christina got to work as soon as she joined the Restoration. She was a fast worker indeed—perhaps that was why Flora was also surprised to hear this for the first time.

“I have no one else I can ask right now other than you, Sir Amakawa. Of course, I am aware that it would be too convenient for us to force the role onto you when we should be bearing the responsibility. However, if you say that you don’t mind facing the hero in a mock battle, could you consider taking on this request at the same time?” Christina bowed in request.

“I don’t mind accepting the mock battle and trying to win. However, I’m not sure if simply winning will be enough to fulfill Your Highness’ desires.”

In other words, whether that would hurt Hiroaki’s pride or not.

“Yes. That is why I would like you to bring out the hero’s true strength, then defeat him to make a show of your power difference.” Christina described her ideal vision. Not an instant defeat, but not a drawn-out struggle either. Essentially, she wanted him to fight squarely and force Hiroaki to yield.

“That’s a rather unreasonable request.” Rio couldn’t help but chuckle.

“My apologies. Of course, I vow that no backlash will fall upon you for your victory, and I shall reward you separately with regards to the escorting matter. You are also free to decline if it is unfeasible, but if you could give it your consideration...” Christina bowed her head broodingly.

“I accept.”

“Thank you very much.”

“Please raise your head.” Rio protested in a slight fluster.

Having her bow her head to me so many times really doesn’t feel right.

Their first meeting had been what it was, and with how their relationship during his academy days was like, he still couldn’t shake off the odd feeling he got from the way Christina was now.

“But what will you do about the time and place?” Rio asked, changing the topic.

“I’d like this mock battle to be held privately. I apologize for the rush, but we’ll hold it in a discreet location tomorrow, before departing for Amande. Lady Liselotte has the perfect place in mind and will show us the way there.”

If they sparred after returning to Rodania, they would attract too much attention from the nobles of the Restoration and leave a bad impression. That was probably why she had gone to Liselotte. It was likely that Liselotte wanted to witness the power of the Divine Arms, too.

“I understand. That won’t be a problem.”

Thus, the date of Rio and Hiroaki’s mock battle was officially decided.

◇　◇　◇

“Then, if you would excuse me.”

Rio left the room with those words, leaving Christina and Flora alone in the room.

“We finally have time to talk alone,” Christina said first. After her conversation with Duke Huguenot, word of Hiroaki’s mock battle reached her ears, so she had to make adjustments for that. Hiroaki and Roanna were present for dinner afterwards, so they hadn’t had any time alone until now.

“Yes,” Flora said, quietly watching her sister’s face beside her. Suddenly, Christina turned her body to face Flora, staring at her closely.

“So, don’t you have something to tell me? About Sir Amakawa.”

“Huh?” Christina’s abrupt question made Flora tremble in alarm.

“You’ve been overly aware of him ever since we arrived at this fortress, and you insisted on following me here like this when I said I was going to speak to him. I thought you had something to say to him, but you barely said a word. That’s why it must be me you want to talk to, and it must be something about him. Am I wrong?”

“What? I haven’t been cognizant of him at all...” Flora awkwardly struggled for words, having been completely seen through.

“So, you’re engaged now,” Christina suddenly mentioned. At a glance, there was no change in her expression, but it looked like she was faking her composure.

“You heard about it?”

“Yes, from Duke Huguenot...” Christina offered no words of congratulations.

“I haven’t thought much about marriage...” Flora hung her head. She was still just a fifteen-year-old girl, after all.

“A woman with a fiance shouldn’t be paying so much attention to a man other than her fiance. While the hero’s ego may be hard to tolerate, that is a different matter. One of the reasons why he’s displeased right now partially has to do with you,” Christina pointed out sharply.

“I-I’m sorry.”

“You can just fix things starting tomorrow.”

“Yes...” Flora responded dejectedly to Christina’s curt words.

She hadn’t wanted to see her little sister make this face. These weren’t the words she wanted to say. And yet, she could only say it in this way. “So... What about Sir Amakawa has your interest? If something’s weighing on your mind, try saying it out loud. I’ll hear you out.” Christina cursed her own incompetence as she addressed Flora in a slightly gentler tone. Now that Flora was engaged to Hiroaki, keeping the fog in her heart bottled up wouldn’t be good for the Restoration’s future.

“I... I said, there’s nothing...” Flora looked like she wanted to say something, but quickly looked down and swallowed her words.

“That’s not what it looks like to me,” Christina said with an ambiguous smile. She had her suspicions, but she wasn’t about to utter them herself without any hard evidence.

After a while, Flora spoke up. “How did you travel here from Cleia?”

“How? We either walked or I was carried while running.”

“Sir Haruto carried you?” Flora’s interest grew stronger.

“No, he didn’t. Sara, the silver-haired girl, carried me. Sir Amakawa carried the two boys that traveled with us,” Christina said with a slightly exasperated laugh.

“I see... Then, what kind of person is Sir Haruto?” It was another sudden and vague question, and about Haruto no less.

“He’s an amazing person.” Christina couldn’t reply with a mean-spirited question as to why Flora was asking such a thing, so she replied vaguely instead.

“Amazing... Yeah, he’s amazing.” For some reason, Flora looked delighted, and Christina was able to guess why.

“Yes.”

So she’s noticed. She’s noticed, and for the same reasons as me, she...

She wouldn’t bring up the subject of Haruto’s identity herself. Instead, she was sounding out whether Christina had noticed too.

What a hopeless child, honestly...

Christina found that a little bittersweet and pitiful at the same time.

It was too obvious like this. At the very least, it was instantly clear that she had feelings towards Haruto. Hiroaki was probably displeased by that, too.

“How do you feel about him?”

“Huh? What do you mean?” Flora cocked her head curiously at Christina’s question.

“What kind of person is he to you?” Christina explained with more detail.

Flora thought carefully, facing her feelings before giving a short reply. “...He saved me.”

“Do you want to do something for him?”

“Yes. Gratitude... Isn’t what I want to do, though.”

“Then what can you do for him?”

“I can’t... do anything.” Flora’s shoulders suddenly slumped, vexed by her own answer.

“Then you don’t have to do anything,” Christina said plainly.

“Huh...?” Flora was stunned.

“If you can’t do anything for him, then that’s fine. There’s no need to be impatient about it. If you force yourself to do something for him, you might end up creating a problem for him instead, no?”

“Right...”

“If you’re still pained by the fact you can’t do anything, come talk to me. I’ll be beside you from now on, so you can vent to me.” Christina nervously moved her hand and patted Flora on the shoulder. Flora had been alone. Her position as a princess meant she couldn’t confide in anyone, so she was isolated the whole time in the Restoration. When Christina realized that, she wanted to touch her. To tell her that she wasn’t alone anymore.

“Can I really...?” Flora asked, looking at Christina’s face.

“Yes. What do you think I came all the way here for?”

“For the kingdom...” Flora answered timidly.

“As a princess, yes. But that isn’t all. I came as your older sister, in order to lessen your burden and protect you. Though I may not be very dependable.”

“T-That’s not true. You’re amazing.” Flora suddenly hugged Christina with a fleeting smile.

“Really?” Christina gently caught her little sister’s body, mouth loosening into a soft smile.

“Yes. You seem to know everything about me... No, about everything around you.” Flora praised her sister while clinging to her adoringly.

“I know you because I’m your sister. As for anyone else, I don’t know everything. But because I’ve observed so many people, I’ve simply learned to predict what emotions people feel at certain times.” Christina had a faintly bitter expression as she patted Flora’s head. She had seen more exchanges between corrupt nobles than she had ever wanted to. Because of that, she thought she understood things—when she really didn’t know anything.

If she had known, she wouldn’t have been cornered like this. She should have been able to conduct things better.

“May I sleep in the same bed as you tonight?” Flora asked, tightening her hold.

“How spoiled of you.” Christina gently patted her little sister’s back.

◇　◇　◇

Around the same time, Rio visited the room where Celia and Sara were staying.

“Excuse me for intruding,” he said before entering.

“Welcome back. How did it go? What did you talk about?” Celia immediately asked worriedly.

“It’s going to be tomorrow after all. There’s nothing to be worried about, so please rest assured,” Rio replied gently.

“I see... But is it really okay? I don’t doubt your strength, but Sakata is going to use his Divine Arms, right? Like Sir Shigekura did...” Celia said, worrying anyway.

“Well, it’s a mock battle, so we won’t be fighting with the intention of drawing blood,” Rio said, glossing over his answer. He expected Hiroaki would attack him by manipulating a phenomenon of considerable scale. In fact, Rio was accepting the challenge with the intention of bringing out the power of the Divine Arms.

“Don’t get hurt...”

“Of course.”

“I don’t want to see you falling down wounded,” Celia said while looking at Orphia. She must have recalled the image of her wounded in the battle with Alfred.

“The same goes for me.” Rio didn’t want to see Celia and Orphia fallen over ever again. Of course, the same went for Sara and the others, too. With that thought, Rio nodded.

“Good evening.”

Light particles gathered in the middle of the room to form Aishia’s image.

“A-Aishia...” Celia and the others were shocked.

Rio was the only one who smiled softly. “So, you were nearby after all.”

“Yup. The stone house has been set up a fair distance from the fortress. Miharu and Latifa are looking after the house. It looks like there was a battle by the border—was everything okay?” Aishia asked.

“A lot happened...” Celia looked at Sara’s group.

“As you can see, nothing is wrong.” Orphia clenched her hand into a fist.

“That’s good to hear.” Aishia’s face softened slightly... Or so it seemed, but it was probably a trick of the eye.

“Just to be sure, are there any soldiers still near the border?” Rio asked.

“Nope. They all retreated to the nearby fortress cities.”

“I see. That’s good, then.” Rui must have kept his promise.

“It’s a relief that everyone is safe. Miharu and Latifa were worried too,” Aishia said, which was why she was visiting.

“Everyone is as healthy as can be, so please tell them not to worry.” Sara cutely flexed her biceps to show off how healthy she was.

“Also, it’s been decided that we’ll head to Amande by enchanted ship tomorrow, then stay one night before heading to Rodania via enchanted ship again. It would be better for Sara, Orphia, and Alma to avoid too much contact with human nobility, so they’ll be returning to the stone house from Amande. Could you pass on that message?” Rio requested.

“Got it. If Sara and the others are returning to the stone house, shall I go to Rodania in their place? I can stay in spirit form as Celia’s guard,” Aishia suggested.

“I would be very grateful if you could do that...”

“Okay. I’ll be off, then.”

Thus, it was decided that Aishia would accompany them after their arrival in Amande.

Chapter 6: A Brief Rest

The next day, before Rio was to depart from Rodania that morning, he visited Christina and Flora.

“In the end, I wasn’t able to settle any of the debt I owe you,” Christina said somberly, seated across from Rio in a drawing room.

Rio shook his head. “You gave me an estate, so I cannot accept any more than this.”

“...I believe the value of your achievement of defeating Alfred is equal to the sword that he owns. And that estate cannot possibly be equal in value to that sword. Thus, I considered giving you Alfred’s sword, but...”

It seemed like she didn’t think Rio had received enough of a reward. The sword Alfred used was a national treasure, which made it priceless in itself...

“There’s no way I could accept a sword like that. Please give that sword to someone worthy instead. I have a sharp enough sword already,” Rio declined politely.

“I understand... In that case, please take this brooch and use it to enter the noble district whenever you come to visit Professor Celia. It will act as an entry pass,” Christina said, removing the brooch she was wearing and entrusting it to Rio.

“Huh...?” Flora, who had been listening silently, made a noise as her eyes widened in surprise.

“What’s wrong, Flora?” Christina asked, but Flora immediately shook her head.

“N-No, it’s nothing.”

“I understand... I shall gratefully accept this.” Rio received Christina’s brooch respectfully. The brooch had the same design as Christina’s official emblem, but Rio had no way of knowing that.

The pause before he accepted the brooch was because he saw Flora’s reaction and suspected that the brooch played a larger role than just an entry pass. However, he couldn’t voice his complaints about a gift being presented by royalty, so he had no choice but to obediently accept it for now.

“Umm, Sir Haruto, you’re heading for Amande after leaving Rodania, right?” Flora changed the subject. She’d probably heard this from Christina, who was already informed of his destination. Incidentally, Christina offered to send him to Amande with an enchanted ship, but he declined by saying he’d run instead.

“Yes. I’ve promised to meet up with Lady Liselotte. As I’ve informed Princess Christina already, Celia will be joining me for this in the near future.”

“Of course, I don’t mind at all. I cannot restrict Professor Celia from seeing her friends—if anything, her expansion of her circle of friends is most welcome for us as well,” Christina said, speaking frankly about the merits to the Restoration without concealing anything.

“Thank you very much. I should be returning to Rodania after visiting Amande, so I can come give you a report along with my greeting at that time,” Rio offered with a slight bow.

“Unfortunately, we may not be available to meet depending on the date that you return. Both Flora and I plan on visiting the Galarc capital at some point in the near future.” It seemed like Christina was also leaving sometime soon.

“Is that so?”

“I must provide an explanation and apology for the deployment of the Beltrum Kingdom’s army by the border, and then discuss various other things. Both Flora and I will be away from Rodania for about half a month or so.”

“I understand,” Rio nodded with another bow.

And here I thought I’d finally have a chance to talk to Sir Haruto... Flora thought in slight disappointment.

Christina observed Flora’s expression with a sidelong glance and closed her eyes in thought for a moment. “However, if you plan on visiting Rodania regularly in the future, we would be delighted to see you again. I shall provide a most hospitable reception for you,” she said.

“I understand... However, there’s no need to provide any reception.” Rio hesitated at the thought of meeting so frequently, but ultimately decided to nod his head for politeness’ sake.

◇　◇　◇

After wrapping up his farewell with Christina and Flora, Rio returned to the mansion first. There, Celia and Aishia were waiting for him. Aishia had probably sensed his approach.

“I know I just came back, but I’ll be going now.”

They had said their farewells yesterday and chatted a lot this morning, so Rio announced his immediate departure. Dragging things out would only make him more reluctant to leave.

Celia sent him off with a smile. “Yup, have a safe trip.”

“See you later,” Aishia stood beside Rio and said to Celia. She was accompanying him part of the way to the outskirts of Rodania, where the stone house was set up.

“You’ll be coming back right after showing Rio where the stone house is, right? I’ll be waiting, so come back soon,” Celia said.

“Yup,” Aishia replied.

“I should be back from Amande in a week or so, so please take care of Celia in that time, Aishia.”

“Leave it to me,” Aishia nodded.

Thus, Rio set off from Rodania.

◇　◇　◇

After Rio left Rodania on foot, he ran down the road for the time being. The city turned into a tiny dot behind him and eventually disappeared. He checked there was no one around and left the main road, taking off using his spirit arts to fly.

His destination was the stone house. Rio didn’t know where it was set up, so he needed Aishia to show him the way.

“Over there,” she pointed out.

They arrived at the stone house several minutes later; they descended at the edge of the rocky area Aishia had pointed at. The door to the house was already open and an excited Latifa was waving her arms over her head at him. Sara and the other spirit folk girls’ contract spirits had probably detected Aishia’s approach in her material form.

“Welcome back, Onii-chan! Aishia!” Latifa launched herself at Rio as soon as he landed, hugging him tightly. She hugged him like she was trying to make up for his long absence, which had lasted several weeks this time.

“Hey. Good to be home.” Rio petted Latifa’s head gently.

“Oh! Is it true Liselotte invited us to her house?! Can I really go too?!” Latifa looked up at Rio’s face and asked innocently.

“Of course. As long as you want to.”

“I want to go! I’ve been wanting to meet her ever since you told me about her!”

“I’m going to head to Amande and meet with Liselotte to adjust the plans, but I wanted to come here first to talk about that. Will you be participating as well, Miharu?” Rio asked.

“Yes, I’d love to... A-Also, welcome home, Haruto. Long time no see.” Miharu first nodded awkwardly, then acted oddly humble, her voice nervous.

“Yes... I’m home. It’s been a while,” Rio replied a little bashfully. It had been several weeks since he last saw Miharu—perhaps that was why he felt oddly shy right now.

“Now, let’s go inside.” Sara clapped her hands and started walking towards the door.

“Let’s go, Onii-chan.” Latifa immediately cut around Rio and grabbed his arm, dragging him inside the house first.

◇　◇　◇

Once everyone sat down on the sofas, Rio decided to bring up the dinner party. “With Latifa and Miharu’s participation decided and Liselotte, Celia, and Aishia’s attendance, all that’s left is to wait for Satsuki to get permission to go out and the dinner party can be held. There should be a total of seven people, including me.”

“Hopefully she gets permission! No, she has to get permission! But...” Latifa was speaking energetically, but then she looked up at Rio’s face and stared.

“What’s wrong...?” Rio faltered under the strange pressure he felt.

“Onii-chan’s saying Celia’s name without using a title!”

Latifa had picked up on it. Sara, Orphia, Alma had faces like they were expecting that reaction, but both Latifa and Miharu were wide eyed at hearing this for the first time.

This again...? It seemed like this topic was a greater problem than he ever expected.

“Why are you doing that?!” Latifa leaned in forcefully.

“We were escorting the princess to Rodania. I couldn’t call her Professor in front of the others,” Rio answered, frowning.

“Hmm... I guess... How nice.”

“I already call you by your name, Latifa.”

“I know that! But suddenly changing the way you address each other makes it feel like you’ve gotten closer!”

He’d been calling her Latifa since the beginning, which was why she was protesting out of envy at being unable to experience the same thing.

“That’s a little unreasonable...” Rio winced.

“Everyone else is envious too, right?! You all want Onii-chan to speak to you like that too, right?” Latifa bluntly asked all the girls present.

Sara, Orphia and Alma exchanged looks. “Well...”

“Well?”

“When we discussed it, we agreed it would be really embarrassing for that to actually happen,” Orphia answered Latifa with a giggle.

“Hmph... I suppose I get that too. As for Aishia...”

“I’ve been addressed this way from the start. I’m fine with this,” Aishia answered plainly.

“I see... What about you, Miharu?” Latifa asked Miharu last.

“Huh? M-Me?”

“Yup! Do you want Onii-chan to call you by your name?”

“H-Haruto calling me by my name...?” Miharu glanced at Rio.

Miharu. Rio’s voice played in her head.

“I-I wonder...?” Miharu’s face was bright red.

“So you do.” Latifa decided by herself.

“T-That’s not true! ...I think?” Miharu refused reflexively, but ended her words with a question.

“Her thoughts immediately show on her face,” Sara said with a slightly scornful look.

“I believe the same applies to you, Sara. Well, Miharu’s case is a little unique.” For once, Alma agreed with Sara.

That’s... That’s because it’s different than being called Mii-chan!

Miharu couldn’t explain this in words, so she protested in her mind.

“Umm...” Rio raised his hand awkwardly. He realized there would be no end to this otherwise. Everyone’s eyes gathered on him. He cleared his throat. “I have a somewhat... No, I have a very serious topic to discuss, so let’s move on for now.”

“A very serious topic...?” Sara’s face turned stern.

“It’s about Latifa...” Rio looked at the girl seated beside him.

“Me?” Latifa blinked.

“Yes, it’s about your past. To be honest, I wondered if it was right to bring it up as a topic of discussion, but if you’re all participating in the dinner party, then I believe it’s something that should be addressed.”

“Sure... What is it?” A slight shadow fell over Latifa’s face, but she nodded with a serious expression and encouraged Rio to continue. She didn’t want to remember her past, but she trusted him.

She knew, unconditionally, that the reason why he looked so torn right now was because he pondered and pondered over this topic before bringing it up. Besides, she knew she didn’t mind the people present right now hearing about her past.

“Sara and the others know this already, but Latifa used to be a slave.” Rio began with the facts, but was immediately interrupted.

“Umm, actually, Miharu knows about that already. I told her before. Including how I was raised as an assassin,” Latifa corrected.

“Really?” Rio asked in surprise.

“Yup. Back when Miharu was still in the village, she consulted with me about whether she should attend the banquet or not. I told her about my past then.”

“I see...”

“Yeah. Sorry for interrupting. Go on, Onii-chan,” Latifa said in a more mature way than normal.

“The truth is... The nobleman who raised Latifa as a slave could be part of the Restoration,” Rio finally revealed.

“Huh?!” Everyone other than Aishia was shocked.

“I-Is that true?” Latifa asked fearfully.

“Yeah. His name is Gustav Huguenot. He is the head of a ducal house, with an eldest son named Stewart.”

“Stewart...” Latifa’s expression turned bitter. She’d never forget that name. He was the one who made her call him Big Brother and came to Latifa’s cell to toy with her whenever he was bored. He never acted too violent to injure her in a way that would hinder her assassination work, but he abused her however he wanted up to being able to treat her with the healing magic Cura.

“W-Wait a moment! Gustav Huguenot—isn’t that Duke Huguenot’s name?” Sara said in a panic, checking if she had the right person.

“Indeed. Other than Princess Christina and Princess Flora, he’s the highest ranked nobility within the Restoration.”

“That man did something like that to Latifa...” Sara gritted her teeth and clenched her fists.

“The possibility is extremely likely, but it’s still a possibility. I apologize for keeping quiet about this. I wanted to explain this matter in front of Latifa, as it concerned her.”

“N-No, we don’t mind that part at all, but...” Sara shook her head at Rio’s apology. She wasn’t able to identify the man herself, as she hadn’t heard anything about his name or face from Latifa. The Collar of Submission that had been used to order Latifa to commit suicide if she was ever questioned was removed, but she still hadn’t told them his name, just in case. However, she would surely be able to identify him by seeing his face.

“I thought it best to discuss this because by attending this dinner party, Latifa will at least gain some kind of connection to nobility. That, and if she ever goes to Rodania with Sara and the others to visit Celia, it’s very likely that she’ll encounter him.”

“I see...” The girls accepted his words with thoughtful looks.

“I’ve hidden the truth of Latifa’s past from Liselotte and informed her that due to certain circumstances, Latifa’s name shouldn’t be revealed to any Beltrum nobles. That’s why the dinner party will be held within Liselotte’s estate with select attendees only. She also went to negotiate with the king for permission to have Satsuki visit her.”

“We didn’t have time to speak to her personally, but she seems like a very good person,” Orphia said softly.

“She is. That’s why Latifa’s secret will be safe with Liselotte if they are to become acquainted in the future, but visiting too often may cause rumors to spread. And so, it would be inconvenient for Latifa to use her current name while in Amande. She’ll probably need to use an alias. That’s why I thought to explain everything properly, as this’ll affect her future greatly.” Rio looked at Latifa. “What do you want to do from here onwards? If you want to go to places other than Amande, you may need to act under an alias like I’ve been doing. I haven’t told Liselotte your name yet, so you can act like it’s your real name. Of course, if you continue living in this house as you have, it shouldn’t pose much of a problem. If you want to go outside but don’t want to be near Duke Huguenot, I’ll do something about it. That’s why I’d like to hear you thoughts about all this.”

He was unusually intense in confirming her intentions.

“Onii-chan...” Latifa bit her lip. It hurt to recall Duke Huguenot, but she was happy Rio had thought about her this much.

“Of course, you don’t have to answer right away. Take some time to think about it,” Rio said, breathing a small sigh to calm his heart.

“I... If I’m allowed to, then I want to see more of the world outside the village. I don’t want to see the person who made me into a slave, but if I can stay beside you as your little sister, I want to travel even more. If I end up seeing that person while going to Rodania to visit Celia, then I’ll endure it. Of course, I’ll have to do it under an alias,” Latifa said, conveying her feelings carefully.

“I see... I understand,” Rio nodded slowly and deeply.

“But I want to meet Liselotte as my real self. I want to see her and have her know about the real me. That’s why I want to visit her as Latifa and not under an alias. Is that okay?” Latifa confessed further, peering at Rio’s face.

“Why wouldn’t it be? If that’s what you want, then we can explain to Liselotte that way. Leave it to me.” Rio assured her with a thump of his fist against his chest.

“Thank you, Onii-chan!” Latifa hugged Rio, overcome with emotion. Miharu and the others looked on with pleasant smiles.

The next day, Rio visited Liselotte’s estate and informed her of Latifa’s thoughts. Fortunately, Francois had given permission for Satsuki to go out, so Liselotte was able to report that the dinner party was to go ahead as planned.

Thus, the date for the dinner party was set to three weeks from then, where Rio had to participate in party games in the name of deepening their relationship. Many dramatic events happened, and everyone had quite the lively, warm, and relaxing time together.

Another week after that, Rio said goodbye to a worried Miharu and the other residents of the stone house, then finally departed for the Proxia Empire.

Rio instantly stepped back to widen his distance with the black flames, watching them dubiously.

“Hmm. On top of being nimble, your reactions are quick as well. However, my sword controls the flames of the evil dragon. It won’t be so easy for you to extinguish,” Nidoll hummed in admiration, then brandished his broadsword in a horizontal slash. The black flames radiated out in a straight line, burning the entire field.

“Hmm... Perhaps I should have held back more?” Nidoll muttered in exasperation at the sea of black. “It has been so long since I’ve crossed swords with someone of equal or greater ability, so I wanted to enjoy myself more... What a cowardly dragon indeed.”

No sooner he muttered that, a barrage of wind suddenly shot out from the black flames. The barrage of wind blew away the black flames, nay, it took in the black flames as it attacked Nidoll in a straight line.

“Hmph!” Nidoll suddenly brandished his sword. The blast of wind made contact with his broadsword and applied creaking pressure to his arm, shocking the air around him.

After a while, Nidoll repelled the barrage of flame-carrying wind. The next moment, Rio had snuck right up to Nidoll.

“Splendid!”

Nidoll had an enraptured smile carved onto his face as he reflexively counterattacked. However, the one with the initiative was Rio, who had launched the surprise attack. He had snuck right up to Nidoll, erasing his distance to the broadsword before swinging his daggers left and right with tricky movements as he began to overwhelm his opponent.

Illuminated by the moon, Rio’s daggers glinted several times. He launched accurate slashes at Nidoll’s arms and legs, but...

The cloth armor he’s wearing seems to have some secret to its material. It’s as tough as cutting a demi-dragon’s skin.

Rio’s slashes were functioning more like blunt attacks. Nidoll’s clothes easily deflected the blades of the daggers. However, it did seem like the damage was building up underneath the clothes. Hits to the vitals were blocked carefully, but it was only a matter of time before he would be rendered immobile.

“Bwahaha, it seems my defeat is coming in only a matter of time. Good, very good. How splendid indeed. I can feel my blood pumping through my veins. Yes, I remember this sensation now.” Despite being backed into a corner, Nidoll laughed loudly without a care in the world. It was as though he loved fighting with every fiber of his being.

Unable to measure the amount of humanity in this man, Rio began to increase his number of attacks somewhat cautiously.

“What’s the matter? This is an opportune chance to come for my head. Come, take this neck in one blow. You’ll only regret it if you try to weaken me first... Ah, it’s already too late.”

Nidoll urged Rio to quickly take his head, but then he suddenly frowned in disappointment. Immediately following, black magic essence violently rose like flames from his body and broadsword.

Rio backed away reflexively, but—

“Unfortunately, time’s up. I cannot hold it back any longer. You should run away quickly,” Nidoll sighed. The violently blowing torrent of black essence gathered around his sword ominously.

That magic essence is bad news.

Rio felt a cold chill down his spine and promptly gathered essence within his body.

“Oh? It seems you intend on exchanging blows with me. Good, good. That way of thinking is truly magnificent.” Nidoll’s eyes widened, showing a glimpse of his astonishment. Then, his mouth twisted with an aggressive grin. During this time, the black essence torrent continued to gather around his broadsword.

“En garde.” Nidoll held his sword pointed at Rio’s eyes, then swung it down slowly, and a tremendous rush of black flames was released. The inside of the arena was covered in pitch black darkness.

However, Rio had gathered a similarly vast amount of magic essence. He raised his hand at the approaching flames without flinching, and white light burst forward from it. The white torrent of light glittered like diamond dust as it rushed straight onwards, colliding with the black flames. Immediately after the collision, blinding light filled the arena and an ice-cold gale blasted through the area.

Nidoll’s black flames had been eaten away and were freezing over. Furthermore, Rio had already moved to approach him from behind.

“Hmm... It was a rather sudden ending, but I cannot recall the last time I felt so elated. Well done. I had fun. To keep my word, I will give you your reward. What do you desire? My life?” Nidoll asked simply. Rio’s dagger was pointed at his neck.

“I have no particular interest in your life. What I want is information.” Rio paused for a brief moment before stating his demand. The reason why he hadn’t attacked Nidoll with the intent to kill was because his original goal was to gather information.

The current situation was definitely not what he had expected, but if this man was the country’s emperor, then it was all the more convenient for him. There was a high likelihood he would know Lucius.

“Oh? So you wish for my truthful answers to your questions as a reward. Is that it?” Nidoll’s eyes widened in surprise.

“That’s right,” Rio nodded.

“Ha. Fine, then. State your questions. Quickly, before the guards come running.” Nidoll smiled in spite of himself and ordered Rio to speak.

“I’m searching for a mercenary named Lucius. If he’s from this country, I want you to tell me what you know about him.”

“...Bwahahahaha!” Nidoll laughed loudly.

“...What’s so funny?” Rio asked with a suspicious look.

“I see. You snuck all the way here in search of that man. An admirable ability to take action, indeed. Heh heh heh.”

“So you’re saying you know of him?”

“Indeed, I do. Though he isn’t a citizen of this country.”

“Then what is his relationship to you?”

“I am the ruler of this country, and that man is the head of a renowned mercenary group. It’s not strange for us to have a contract connection,” Nidoll answered boldly and heartily.

“In that case, you must know of a man named Reiss too? The one acting as the ambassador of this country.”

Nidoll’s eyes widened faintly. “Hmm, so you know of Reiss as well. Indeed, I was the one who appointed that man as our ambassador.”

“What is Reiss and Lucius’ relationship?” Rio asked flatly.

“Lucius was once tasked with Reiss’ protection, but I have no interest in the relationships of my retainers. Reiss rarely returns to this country as is. Even when he does return, he disappears without a word shortly after. Well, it seems he’s making various moves forming factions and the like... Hmm. So which is your target, Lucius or Reiss? I will only give you information about one right now, so choose wisely.”

“Do you understand the situation you’re in right now? I’m the one asking the questions.” Rio shifted his hand quietly, pressing the dagger against Nidoll’s throat.

“Now now, boy. I told you the patrols will come running soon. Do you have the time to waste?”

“Then tell me Lucius’ location. If you know where he is, that is.”

“The Paladia Kingdom. The kingdom is constantly in conflict with their neighboring countries, but my country is providing support behind the scenes. It’s a small kingdom to the east. Have you heard of it?”

“I’ve heard the name.”

“Then I’ll keep this short. It was roughly one year ago that his contract ended with me, and he chose the Paladia Kingdom as his new job location. I prepared a letter of recommendation in secret, so he should have a connection to the royal family. I don’t know if he’s still working there, but the first prince may know something,” Nidoll replied, then gave a small shrug.

“...” Rio fell silent with a pensive look. Nidoll was voluntarily giving him information, but without credible evidence, there was no telling whether his words were true or not. Rio hesitated, wondering whether it was right to leave like this, when—

“Well, it’s your choice whether you believe me or not. But what will you do now? I’ve told you everything I know about his location, so your reward has now been fulfilled. I have no obligation to obey you any further than this, yes? And it seems the patrol is here. Right on time,” Nidoll sneered audaciously. Like he said, the passage connecting to the arena was starting to fill with noise.

Staying any longer would indeed be too risky, huh?

Rio furrowed his brow faintly, then decided to retreat.

“Ah, one more thing. If you’re leaving, leave through the way you came in. Don’t go touching the barrier carelessly. Though it’s up to you whether you believe this or not, too,” Nidoll added as an afterthought. At the same time, magic essence swelled up within his body. Rio reflexively stepped back to gain his distance, then immediately began running to escape.

What was the deal with that man?

Rio leaped while running, making his way up to the spectator seats. He had an eerie feeling that was difficult to describe in words, making him glance back down at Nidoll.

Nidoll smiled up at Rio boldly.

“There he is!”

“He’s fast!”

“There may be others! Protect His Majesty!”

The soldiers scrambled around in a flurry, surrounding Rio with coordinated movements as they commenced their escort of Nidoll. However, Rio ran at a speed faster than they could follow, lightly leaping up to the atrium.

“W-What physical abilities he has...”

“Is he an enchanted sword user?”

The soldiers froze and looked up at Rio in amazement.

Rio looked down at Nidoll one more time before leaping out of the arena, disappearing from the view of the pursuing soldiers.

“H-He jumped?!”

The soldiers were all wide-eyed in shock. Rio took that chance to use his wind spirit arts and ascend rapidly, leaving the barrier through the gap. Meanwhile...

“Don’t be so mad. I merely put on the act that Reiss directed. I made quite the actor, don’t you think?” Nidoll muttered, chuckling heartily to himself.